[{"topicId":"18","id":"18000","langCode":"en","question":"kKi6sjbnoNKQpjgIHHGcPhVhep/P25Xbnt4hMWyXWU4CkxjvP6+gidd73PvTjOVc3BArlDF+chZdo2C9SbvGvQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["whose","where","whom","who"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zTD6uZKNKBQfG1aUkzpTj+nkfqwgq7VmouC4D+fDzxNDLm6wPJJjE86zT0BblKr6qMvC9thivJ3SI6C9a3YSiDr/GQhpC6T1Z71fF3Z0XkTzxwKgTkTEVphMxTcs83T9UTe+7uS1n1r58pgpbjyrUC4IiVTkoLaDreASKZUe4JJdFPKGK3zU3H+M/0AhBzf51q0NvC3CG+bONmt6eDME/bx9GszdhLkcz6b4LlkWPyT/2F7IPltg4tkY13mEWXtG1eeWFbecmBX9VFECkb+zazM5QBCRlB9amuMdNKNGfW5SO225xEvBRL8ET6dTlv0ggC3p2NGacmLELzbA3Jmeh9Hqvez0vOc+zvKJJHvpx6g0OmFx+hxYZYgig3HN247PB/nI1a6hagvIj6lt8+Ey0X7h3TFdwQSoHqe1zfXMd5K4xipeYYv4h3kx7MGtltorVNtDTUdShgXln7paNb88nhxc3uo58/pq4qiiLG1LA7VLvI9l9+GOP1XJLszNAJR9BrrZ73uylwBcC1UVNfE8PrFyWEglf02lmNGmExI63bviZx4UM7qxfggcE4Y1dl9BusUefvxE9w+KKhvUGLPxK2z9C99kq2ECIWxjsYsAV3HHvVlVayHM8du3oTOjzyJQmPOk3WbRBoNR/GBsmCdXhgu8j2X34Y4/VckuzM0AlH0Gutnve7KXAFwLVRU18Tw+l8adnjIeFwM19XZa1Av0e0S7UH+vIfSn6zjlQRDsMkhgZpKu8gMLgQhV3+6k2jjLOY/3CVtJoZxx/qvgyEc9IY\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18001","langCode":"en","question":"+VZgPPlr95UGA5YKaPYjpzqX0HCRXZrmJAkNeXVFTQgrUW46lFfDjoUJ20sd+t2bMMiNVd3foIIk9wwWL8612A\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","whom","who","when"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zTD6uZKNKBQfG1aUkzpTj/1ZoEXRzK+9UZtQFkE6kJB+7ks4PcEBbhg8JBorMpwo8tPPlEupMHXSuc7S/wO+2zTlVWKnytp/u0n+LjJkJAdrLHq8DW7qmwVSPDLdyC5VgPrI2bUA67IA0pb/OV1BXQYf+Bc8PRITV99dm0mW+xsdTInrZM5gcR3gbmFCoiKFJvW7v/UuiYBWr6F3LbIaPTKjKZroc5UCxhXhNM9d2yvUIc6B2SzT2z/POphb9aZZYE89ZCkVq7mcgHWRIaXS5rIh+GLtq27/R52KPDVHkRvzQIn4ArMIFvY/peHoG7g4Lwf+oiLFf7kTpBdVvHj1y2HNbuaWU5nVZKK6HqXst9kri6QDyhL24074n4hQckozDgtf9uxbRsQgMNZkHyC7ejbjanbnJggeU0E8HcoHoLBC6VtCuKXd9duv7NR4ifOotWOELDfNy+ueG8fmiep5clnNubr8iYxnyC3TykB4MnBxWX87vB+/inruD4Kk0+IJDWkOgofmP+oVkUMdghwav9Do8Yn1V5ogo+CI7r5NEcrQY7Y0GTsXEW7XtF394OQluCfYw6RmxgWdzkH74LZeOsqB2cMIPXiFBwI6Iqn4CR9uSpe02Z7K6+hgXBD/oIW+wowUl3HAoon+if5ODrj73wQ1AOUao2F2bRiRj7fpJBKdtpr/dVKEk/gR4hfTWu4A9+/gqJANdyz8x02+lCHLxtakP1vmA+V7s5F/FwL35Zo5yZPYCVxLuz4kweqRrPMmg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18002","langCode":"en","question":"9AAUh6RMUFl+9Iv1LLoDrBDxCfDsG/nSjs2K8G9sDYw6BScE0OAR1mZsoFHSX4N1NJA0cubaD66jscZlmxDyUBr4msVP72Fr5rOgWKlPM9g\u003d","answers":["whose","whom","who","whose"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zTD6uZKNKBQfG1aUkzpTj8nu/VQ0pnJUPx23KMH6zsk/j0qrxObMSC41f4y+7ltW1JzRANSZj5WECcUK018o5gcA5SQ5FkCkUf44sTnLB/cPy8KB1rCLuRiqG11vh6PQfFht1S73KwWqLLGNaW/bZ/+a4YveagKDu06CjvBwsti7OBP46LZAdVg2Lp3oI0kiJoyKtxfoJm36/wBVrCC1yPWMV/dDYQ36LQjUBqBBaaXfgDxrR33AQG1dxkudg2bbAadCFHCsHkkKERDJX+axjyLfF/vouj9viXhk6KSuwuu79NRudUEHAyPyJeDB5rvcf/RogBqCRHiME0/YmIq6GMYuukqtO/mv0eRChcoas87kPibXK3tiLdflK/4D0BZI3/zNwoGBEcgFvkR79ZWEGhKsFpAr/qRiGGSoWABT0vOnu8wNWdM/4Bscb4mfva+s1wxST3ycU+aRI8sFUcek4hyO4r/jLgHgYY2Eq6Rj9vcplArvZJCTrEBq7ivBkPQTrSvOpAqpPOJVdTKHOenK0TA6Jfa6KCpdSTFtpNskNg0/13KOrbDYdczBmyoRzmfepwiFmA2obXSabuSLuLPYkQ9z+U0Npfu2gPpJRbxjx1adew6fnDsi2SC1XbqrRxT4ruvJ+lmUTzysnDCEsy1W/fVMVaYmjIHIKPv7lS/sHDbhmTlQFC2urLTFzD8LjQll/HwZCaVerQygCSvIF6I0C6II+NC6Ruqj27CYWXryGwXdPVIropwo3Tj+DjkVJD2F3RbRQBGJmYIXv+dQa5Zf5HjL6EiZCRpl064JwIXq2P/6ZnaG91ZEI4gcmOfXKiVsafE7IeSIv0AtVqeZZX8OdFKDzoXfgH4+ysFhezxQ1B83jjOmlFnldweDihmvUTcCDQz6PvjXkRajbiNwFgrSo2EbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18003","langCode":"en","question":"SS6NUt0Mla+2hLN5cNYDcQDHGq894wAlgqbOTiv1BzryUNrNI1KHzjeijWDvMZegQ6NEbeyh+e6ek7KDx8T52lBc2aJg3qKkKE1IZIOz4AqEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["who","where","whom","whose"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zTD6uZKNKBQfG1aUkzpTj+nkfqwgq7VmouC4D+fDzxNgOMd8XcCt5zPeqI+rPIUKaM+kMs4OkAn+EDkq6zy/B8fOyZBO9NtXJzc1tmKpR2ADjjCdOI9sGsjb9maHfAqllCG09X0ux9ObNwj/DtoOCBfIFB9syA0/yTOmi8t9zvZl+HUNS+ez4eXHpMMF90iBlgPWze9IqV3O561I76x+pHtCyXQwMLdleIREPJy414SCTwo1tPvKce6HSYWZXYvXyuk5PxyGk2ebrcK8qBZUigxxt6ZC9xozfRtCDv8xmepRWunN+FC6+E65T61k8OBQxvJGyQ+wHdkJZzGSCsZa0rKJO8GXeGOg+5aTffy86mCQEC58xlMrP4ra+m45wZ/5KD1SRdok54yNbffEQYUT7wF1OyqKgg+hjK2fDwrkCvvYeae6BwqJOY/38ocI+tyJH+NFfcyQ59j2demSuE3KHBeNdQnhfECFj56G8U7C15ywpz6omZlzbg4qt1fB1jHWixeZvTKR5rs1iQo1JNowKUL8EVz7zZS2VvhLE8CVaX/HULzU57WDGsHSxXQ2rSXVacXweFZt/Hp/pVN0pfSlBwiWTU+Yrn1Kc5Fss0sEFfKHt32BjvcYOECsbLmJVJqtK3y+aJMmYM2dUrYEP8sG8jCnPqiZmXNuDiq3V8HWMdaEWYpJG0G2yoOlHc7Hc1tmNGUlC349jkOsR2rb3zXcGlXpR2k5C5WlZ9Yi7h0Ih/5wF51A+3T8OjmKz1dJGT30W1aawp06nVJ+uOCm3DuMt4\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18004","langCode":"en","question":"BQGfVayxWz9E8uGMKfsneID1O5NU3hLn5GMdP/JW3AfG9U3jY3CyMWkyXlMi8jLFF5RzjQ7IBLCarwfOAyLnkLfSOJxQ1xEoENTc+9lVi/o\u003d","answers":["whom","when","which","who"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zTD6uZKNKBQfG1aUkzpTj8nu/VQ0pnJUPx23KMH6zskVFn3uoHAHM+HAvgvt2zVBBIEbaVdRJz518ZHKpOZtlMffQnecBkcQYPfBDcmwTZaCq+D1NTLFvZOE3t/2ngo2eyBearEzAtKpDdCYgDf8xmlwarPU5QyRNq6kbTqqfkumOOZfSBJuVgCdgin91Nq4V8wj/6td26+4gS76f/SJhJhCyj0p1FMdT3fgSLA0qKqZC+WTdGOdgV7/Ja1J0uEhql8wXtUP+27XgAesp3xebMY0v/R/gbFew5lC/svf5fBeBDMrem2Nrg7vcwKtQEZKHVTahfdtdtkmQNTZ2GuLskz16DYkB+R5FH1fo8V57GsaibUmjtfuvWj3kYaXkn9h+cFCJ3uJlQjfVw0Rj0nyC246WKJSbFNtKXC/WmAlMnALZKcY90Pf8ngmgtHntmOGRUBaCseV9Mzxipli5lGCb26b7OwB34UqTNT3b2E53Ryro4aDztRFvg7yMwDhLfOBKfY5EpmMSlDDNognz0rMAFjKYr/0Jbw30h9H6ZDVZH7NoDVVlcAPXiSBSRLNsCvHHiAtFgDNiyClH1QuGSdJeku8j2X34Y4/VckuzM0AlH0ktUdlNCPg74CkOnFm9QbCqVPVbHH78JPlF0UQywcYccS7UH+vIfSn6zjlQRDsMkhyuFUxRzORp89cELZ/2sih7RwSQ+8AFxgPOuYmYZ3F3EhsBSlFQ4xYLwb/OXCgYObjk5YEVBsdBwJA8uY5VdA7w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18005","langCode":"en","question":"xLPOl5f71sVRpOy722hH4LsWmdpFbMtF5JknmFzexjQ6YHJJ7UeJrXyksyu4fz2JnHjxo4ysWWl2XllcNEBHZw\u003d\u003d","answers":["when","who","which","whose"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zTD6uZKNKBQfG1aUkzpTj8nu/VQ0pnJUPx23KMH6zskIFWvVW5hR4c08H36cKg5lxIEbaVdRJz518ZHKpOZtlOnjAjOqbT5BP2ydSvMrxHYCq+D1NTLFvZOE3t/2ngo2eyBearEzAtKpDdCYgDf8xmlwarPU5QyRNq6kbTqqfkumOOZfSBJuVgCdgin91Nq4V8wj/6td26+4gS76f/SJhJhCyj0p1FMdT3fgSLA0qKqZC+WTdGOdgV7/Ja1J0uEhql8wXtUP+27XgAesp3xebMY0v/R/gbFew5lC/svf5fBNacVZXvq7ziNe318rD8MCIS7xap99/+5owqZS5QER62KSE0grnH3sV5qsT9ewgYMeupZNS5K17iAYk75JjJIcoVnKmxOO8XcX7gM96nmDQEiqQGCuUf3obuEOkP2Utjytea6tX5sbZrhSy4+mBOSY7CJofShqZw37++DlcerQqnCmugs9I5/t3O8tco7354SALenY0ZpyYsQvNsDcmZ6H0eq97PS85z7O8okke+nHqDQ6YXH6HFhliCKDcc3bjs8H+cjVrqFqC8iPqW3z4TLRfuHdMV3BBKgep7XN9cx3krjGKl5hi/iHeTHswa2W2itU20NNR1KGBeWfulo1vzyeHFze6jnz+mriqKIsbUsDtUu8j2X34Y4/VckuzM0AlH0Gutnve7KXAFwLVRU18Tw+sXJYSCV/TaWY0aYTEjrdu+JnHhQzurF+CBwThjV2X0G6xR5+/ET3D4oqG9QYs/ErbP0L32SrYQIhbGOxiwBXcce9WVVrIczx27ehM6PPIlCVPyE2sktSDTm4CFFgNUeK4gj40LpG6qPbsJhZevIbBd09UiuinCjdOP4OORUkPYXdFtFAEYmZghe/51Brll/keMvoSJkJGmXTrgnAherY//pmdob3VkQjiByY59cqJWxp8Tsh5Ii/QC1Wp5llfw50UoPOhd+Afj7KwWF7PFDUHzeOM6aUWeV3B4OKGa9RNwINDPo++NeRFqNuI3AWCtKjYRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18006","langCode":"en","question":"hGtivfJIglFnIuSVynbprSW+pnM5A4B4Uc0DB3O0QK5SRJWtg1GMQSiFvBqcuNBekOFRpM6D1yMmqJM9+HxXvoRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["who","which","whom","whose"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x15QKaZSgMriiWfMGuQwZ6SJc/MvTI0EOoRytJSpXrChbQ9QmlevZ0TPZGyPFLVeYPg9OSBSryxmjcT9FTD+JJDtP9ppKhzm2B8LLyXqrilCzeBWUxYs/qC2UMbDw4W+++gJ22R7ytsL3whWmxPt5HX5JFIqtW8swdDPLRB1rEtQIkSFRUnPid+qXQNFj96aqdMKp1RMLoVpbLi+U3wVhkqztiQN4+E6ynm86Eq/2mvSWJ4GkAAxIKaXOU6QYBpzoXH3Hu7ewXTxMvXMywiBj0MbfTB937hWhB4PWbME1KXVirSsyFpa8eQHlxv9RJDHUeu18P4CqjD7Kdk6usSTWtvUipDkJ1hMZ2Nr6kw+UEDI9+RprJnJvwv5bRLqAES7SU4yfYMSE3ZBFD07L9Tzf1xAN/n26WDvAU7v979Ys4UTSzkK9IPB/5QZLdfsMg7XFMD9KnT4pSLDFpornlRvMzlTsfbH2CYn2pqHtzmgWmGIWTDpL2zBh4/489a5bIo53PXc0w43NIoZSusT/xly8Dl7+mZSo8jrvJ+gxbj+RwphxJqTsac8/6Q2ykTOlkNfW4gC3p2NGacmLELzbA3Jmeh9Hqvez0vOc+zvKJJHvpx6g0OmFx+hxYZYgig3HN247PB/nI1a6hagvIj6lt8+Ey0X7h3TFdwQSoHqe1zfXMd5K4xipeYYv4h3kx7MGtltorVNtDTUdShgXln7paNb88nhxc3uo58/pq4qiiLG1LA7VLvI9l9+GOP1XJLszNAJR9BrrZ73uylwBcC1UVNfE8PrFyWEglf02lmNGmExI63bviZx4UM7qxfggcE4Y1dl9BusUefvxE9w+KKhvUGLPxK2z9C99kq2ECIWxjsYsAV3HHvVlVayHM8du3oTOjzyJQsb00z3tQEjLl8FAJW03MU4\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18007","langCode":"en","question":"6mrgSlX3G10777NioOfrrD851BOvyZpuBsUWWz0PQkxqzKtOP6LyXHzljI1/gz5eLCHXKjBWjM2cqsOP2k4v2ygXDQS73lFRl6k0qjZDTVU\u003d","answers":["whom","who","which","when"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zt+6O+bxq5wQnD8AWnfwOze16vZHYJAe4xBu9b7n8d3+ToEvrewWbv8DLx5NLw5El4GIx8dEMJL2bZhiARmoE6L8pnt1rq23f+yKogMOVagYjo3DLFQbT5SgxzWdxdbJIPaM+CW0W8qfAe9Ny+z0g//kGnyDd/febiqq4b3Nvj6hKDt4fCzOR2XWTMcx0rJVj3eRW785wGv0qE0kzS7EWhZ2lQRtFfMIpuQ3cPeSu6Qxn/GwRhvNrfJCLQhQgn+6Tla2E4UlKcmW5ey+NHTD8v3iYbO523X5hmydOVHQXGBXyBQfbMgNP8kzpovLfc72Zfh1DUvns+Hlx6TDBfdIga41gHBoFIXQM7Ms1LxJRd0UjuMABVOeZi9A7qR9gvkPLud25mn6Zv2xsAZz77RC7+HzHvdSDlXsK5X+gU1BthDJ5I0ZvhyOBYCSjeG7ABPHTkfdffEqrWr3W3o6pcmJzeQawOyeacOhniidsm1eJk/5B3g0QUbJpC/sp0MvXQLQHl6490mxlKWVw1c1v4nZE9P9qtavmVIGCVAJcjFjnGV7nLGDSjWoUsMi/HSeXQ0M4qL6BO3r53bLmQdrVJxojHCQAB1SfsfgFANNCtJLp6c/hcmXM/LBZT9YPmt+gXARNA0cg+nO23F9gSazDGh7oQUGEtpRkEE0Nw33sNRJH6aU3rGh7AiDojIi8tHtJB7aJM/XObvRB9alorfdkxVPPgjgvZ9pQZfFM27oaZP21tV"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18008","langCode":"en","question":"TF36YqxFQd2aLVC5Emz2bhgkYr4D7mdS/f1csEj8l67ujAfEwmBM8MaMhZ27ylQsEijVgxSdil0yUcWQUf0jXw\u003d\u003d","answers":["whose","who","whom","where"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zt+6O+bxq5wQnD8AWnfwOyip3BnmTn5JNBBfeVAUkmniCbeXBzes+pu4gCN2KZQAehACpyHYRcBtWCBu6CgG3LuUoddJHhuYk+nBxLjSoppK3HJo9+fSwqyQNHCcpEHLkeS/BTEBBlqgsEgPJDHy/x+x4QItGxqpymfwgDmEMvCbsKs+PrIUfKOC41gtf/uf3giD1X0lSM7TwQ9eTC2NcmVL/I4OHoFJXY+StBACvf2zQIn4ArMIFvY/peHoG7g4Lwf+oiLFf7kTpBdVvHj1y2HNbuaWU5nVZKK6HqXst9kfTce6SN16v7s1q3LEXbQOs/kpCPNuowyYztYNjghLRTitA+stBu2A11toBcPagfh7LXN+N4AnmyxK9phsq7m5Yyw43zosN0QjnU8sMOU7nP2WwSBy8qqO6t4Y9UV5cQWOs1yOrAUh66GFPfZR0GjU9UOCRSX8uKVWcS0k11EyjvhTwWfzy+YB5JgCn0WRY/Rq4m1Gr7xwvSa8YG06VNDvhSkoiESQ5Y4J45wvMgEqLWRmq5K4/P7eYKqcwbq23HYCjBSXccCiif6J/k4OuPvfLrWIjs3Fd5Ok6/5s5DnNqKQ8kqGyp2bMNzQFqoJrEixiMljyQSQMxTuWoDq5khhd8hxAuyhvZ370Pm6nfEtRhEWSHikWz3kwtRL0HRtUPUsFKSiIRJDljgnjnC8yASotcBrMcKKHZgyLxZ+NmVN1hGJnHhQzurF+CBwThjV2X0GgFis0yLrBLYzSE8FFtlEunMuGVVLsg/qhpYNPyGFJmQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18009","langCode":"en","question":"DDRLLoVdem9E1+elOeOruBTc7GONOPMMflShL08vJGSHCn6YbJXPPbzq3nJ5iInsh4vEKtPYBM+tlMcCaKB8OA\u003d\u003d","answers":["whose","when","who","with whom"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19fG+Zptm9IObuKWfEz8XfRMulSRfk7EvjGQZTgK0rA3ZOSdl9HJCzIquOopHTbC2hdmdbBN5lARNkVok0pFMr+GZOVAULa6stMXMPwuNCWX/cPBHn7qsS7mUQUWAS3Xog/5b6xuV9W8GJYpdb9Dg69i1cZSPUORq8SVwtKmlxOsCDbGCBkdyxwU3PiBE2ws3OfCu+mTuLx4fBBkOdNIMUgFThhTY/MKUpzfYQakuZ5umNNCUHf95t3AZVd2hk37JnKQuQ6wGYYu8XaUOiidM8wih+aE2NPgm1nz0zhQSVBSwPw1Oc0vA0UZX4aGa5xrpUBpYmaRYwl8beyTAnwn16S9P71qQLnwcu+SXIRoHZ42O0SUxza7C/IV3eov0qLsUuT7Cexqk3w5dusmDDW2aw+iUcVmSroShkNSX6Xks/1QAXc/a1HJ+ASMbwJ+LDRk1kOn0DYx+DXfLEgbSRZuUrD+anwkzUg04euSrTPTgb1cjn1zcLqddVyfI8u+h1QXj0sZgyY1Vkm9xF38Q0XJ9rP9zw3TZ5EEm8TgcetTweaLgMsccvmOxRNEtL37ONvlvU6jyZmnqBl4eqtohG4Xe4KNELksMXGf93WUsZOkeNZHIbVcJZZlEiqk2Z1MxA0a+sJLFo1z2OFa1paATSqu1I+dZX1+oF40GRDesQhsG85gwgTTss7zQAiMVhD53hlDuN1urpZ45CBZZrhnHoonLC/yS0whcbhh5N9Og8QFddafuA+IOJN/q7oOJY9K20tb2viqQfAKWSmAjfSRLXK2xSvAO3+TnGtUrvbxl5voo4iKu8v2qUMc2tuV8IOHIL0nyIQOKET60ySezdTsUV9wPvbIE2iWPBhRzNPL6Onj4FQXYPhiPihn8Glju0cEhmPAp9rShTVrqLN6SFDl8U735I8swq9YlJgDC3fS8mi0B9tmLB4qvnuspAYKzguj1XZqfJd51YxHxf4O4Q1oLkvyh+bcs0TF2HzeWg9vrVpW0tviXa2+UrjdNmgmJ66JnJaTBVbTeTfvWEA/YXCopf4X14YkI+458P1L/5JXzKrIEV8SHIdGVSMfcugYs2MEljQiug\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18010","langCode":"en","question":"fXbCntNX6EAgkObfrsykEjXvORQp2UkiUEGfpcbreur4pp1yuEy7v3/4p9m5MpODyqg/f5oz+i7nejVgZqwlo10ioYFk1fz3XIXRBDNA/AQ\u003d","answers":["where","when","which","who"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zTD6uZKNKBQfG1aUkzpTj+HOCOqWdf/zf3ieHpo1Shah31KBLNRcF0cfYa/2sS7opmZKY88vSCXjVJGZYOFLscE8k43VMGzC20O9kFqTi9XxproemiM5/Hx1PFYQCW+ww+H3358IvuOVgRtxvUzxB8ec8OHUyZArUzR4C3KugSuVwC5S7c2ZDS0+6CB8wpOSf2kzlyUF6DKr/ozipFSLx+73qfFixvsA+kREkYXddEBDbmze+yFsgfvVTgPoIihl5vaMvMYbmQotiz+CGKAjvXpMtjxNpv7bLGiyO/HZX1gS1pIWskzhJtS8gGv4sLmWBDgtYwpkaFp/ADWeYonRSp3BDIgvbJSJ0nS00DXe3AkP+qmhHipxv+zqH2ZPacS2EBhfonsIycuEoB22gMzbz3Xbb/qvpAU9e5GkLXwb5SbC5UG1ddTfykVwEzbEcSV/ufFQrDQVOdL1ZF8P4hwiHhrNB7ocCzra/659kuPMn0LvVUMnoSlC4UYEwWZcMir1J3Q13OxzIjqWU6yIdb2d/VkZW++3XBByLRf2A8iPYdyQPBppkkKFxnzhopjBghknMDol9rooKl1JMW2k2yQ2DSlmuVMMmZH3o2iJ6hbz9yOKJb4TCA3nXeivBQCO7Pp+yLGqzg25FtuMce9wa6l5R37WIzdcOELqkF8EcNA5x/N1eEg0TSYmP/FZFLSAjE6Nkkl50IVb0HaXCaXW4r7cjMcilaRC91BclK53y5LDQPEketpwY49RazNbXfoUWtIMUGNtikrhnOD5qyuSQliNQk1U5PD4KogT0vqyRUXxkQG+z8zu/CgmS+zyTGQI88mePyxs2/llqEGFwQFr7sYx74\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18011","langCode":"en","question":"JqR2Pj3twCNFc1CoptSdAGZA6IM3cEzjkl4N8CwhbRHp5CzcR/MK5pFckTxkTHN+mRgzbrQsbely03xn46HIjA\u003d\u003d","answers":["when","which","who","with whom"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19fG+Zptm9IObuKWfEz8XfRMulSRfk7EvjGQZTgK0rA3gOjmuDIcAvV2SnHHMv3QzZYFIJpW+7gCkV7h/eiX5/MsKo2906I2+OPFS+eVfkgd+pYei20ZPvghAkPpEA9/XnMJqLzRo/Uk0Vbh6u9k6h5S2oxdQITb5Ih3vtuFguOzjn1zcLqddVyfI8u+h1QXj0sZgyY1Vkm9xF38Q0XJ9rP9zw3TZ5EEm8TgcetTweaLxGDpFucNMjySEkX4gnzXs1zaUZG9Y8tTCszwmWWvCum2Kt+5+QVArzdtoCLkxb1gJzeB7ni+GUhYvgbuftal+JbT93DdK/5SPUuwb9bkjAty2FGmECdeK2TCeNZ0F9p4TP8egMjyS2BhmepY8IiD7obnA1I3RVtkOhg+cmQPm9bzbUafZSsF+1wccbKSiIgaKJPl74bQAwtKf6VSd9VRBuE1+FfgnUmuAGTM07UdHn0+Pq45zjjWQmidvXJb419NUDGcCuTMDE6qzwwU+fzm3hK8hMyMy1Jjp3ERU4zKETWSuHMp5dXLxE5YxWD7/r+Xfm4bJVbRrQa8wzvl0+Ca7J3Q13OxzIjqWU6yIdb2d/UEkXFOUmtMWmA59PZ//clutehLpW++vG/JCZVkPN3AF8Dol9rooKl1JMW2k2yQ2DTO/Sj3hUX3SqyuCbTr8ZqANOT5H6eFnCgoGj+4VGfuKQ0Ko+n63oB4CYfXmc9alZ+sjG9Ga59eIUueXbaNN3Tg5wUIne4mVCN9XDRGPSfILbjpYolJsU20pcL9aYCUycAtkpxj3Q9/yeCaC0ee2Y4ZFQFoKx5X0zPGKmWLmUYJvbpvs7AHfhSpM1PdvYTndHKujhoPO1EW+DvIzAOEt84Ep9jkSmYxKUMM2iCfPSswAWMpiv/QlvDfSH0fpkNVkfs2gNVWVwA9eJIFJEs2wK8cr84Bm72dWRqi4l8Z6wOOZg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18012","langCode":"en","question":"IFaR/zHCjqKdg4yNiGPjhAeT06+avj5kAn5sNQpqrwz3N1j6q4kKdxy0eTcJlrFhxUhpi78ZIigtWN3VE6Z4zoRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["whom","when","which","who"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14rnKqztzRrbOuE1I8sk+AlX7I1qbCKkVBAFRlVBWxLdENmXLjaIBHSNk+OR5NprZzgtf9uxbRsQgMNZkHyC7ejbjanbnJggeU0E8HcoHoLBC6VtCuKXd9duv7NR4ifOotWOELDfNy+ueG8fmiep5clnNubr8iYxnyC3TykB4MnBxWX87vB+/inruD4Kk0+IJDWkOgofmP+oVkUMdghwav9Do8Yn1V5ogo+CI7r5NEcricIO6Abz/ysrgggbwkUJZcO0/ULQ29J7dCcwl/aclgV6gn7rR7xrwM1f/JgGJ+djBZhqsCiPnwL96czdIQW9cE+K0BvPGruK8Poa9Fhk//F8r3d7TSsWMk6SQo4zUnFS/muGL3moCg7tOgo7wcLLYuzgT+Oi2QHVYNi6d6CNJIiaMircX6CZt+v8AVawgtcj1los98wZm+SoRsK2QjQo5qCNiN6k9bn953pLa9Tj8nVLz7E2/sTXjhR3QSQH4zZGUDGcCuTMDE6qzwwU+fzm3hK8hMyMy1Jjp3ERU4zKETWSuHMp5dXLxE5YxWD7/r+Xfm4bJVbRrQa8wzvl0+Ca7J3Q13OxzIjqWU6yIdb2d/UEkXFOUmtMWmA59PZ//clutehLpW++vG/JCZVkPN3AF8Dol9rooKl1JMW2k2yQ2DTO/Sj3hUX3SqyuCbTr8ZqANOT5H6eFnCgoGj+4VGfuKQ0Ko+n63oB4CYfXmc9alZ92IbAIspgYQhAib0ZwCgI5"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18013","langCode":"en","question":"Yp/pPgTgyzSgmeg8U2PuYE2EYkM6tFg8JpPac2Q99YLCH1TS+bO+5Ig8H144te6S","answers":["where","when","who","which"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14rnKqztzRrbOuE1I8sk+AlX7I1qbCKkVBAFRlVBWxLd2iCjBttSqYO5e01DM/NAaqaxXXLqXHCqbD3VG7KpNWWnVExZrTKtxVc86QS+RX5c5tlIvqxb3PQ0krV3LTDdITDcttzaZ8lKXqbfeDrHFbAFtJTCWrP0WVM0HWhsKHZXBfBp96hoTeMtWImd/ThMRX+wswEaY9oRce6U8SXhqptXEFhZYuH4WjkiXOrOhlQpkZ0YJawzgcyt3JYEAGfAIjjVkBHeUbW02TZoqq8vP9TADcHaaVUqy0hL7gokLdScfPt68K71Sq+rddzWtkc7nrLlbJiNWEJ3Kf8NctqO8tkZA6LZhjg+dFfT3xLCw4x69qlX2x6Y7rUi6LzF1/iru92X7Sr0RvVSkTkEVTgLiJKBCMobeZvyGz8/qOgpdrDC9muWbt0tMUeZw0hsVvrZZq/TziAAsDVTbeiUgbpBWHEmg9U1XxWC6DgLJiFfyRDDndDXc7HMiOpZTrIh1vZ39WRlb77dcEHItF/YDyI9h3JA8GmmSQoXGfOGimMGCGScwOiX2uigqXUkxbaTbJDYNKWa5UwyZkfejaInqFvP3I4olvhMIDedd6K8FAI7s+n74J9jDpGbGBZ3OQfvgtl46yoHZwwg9eIUHAjoiqfgJH25Kl7TZnsrr6GBcEP+ghb7CjBSXccCiif6J/k4OuPvfBDUA5RqjYXZtGJGPt+kkEp22mv91UoST+BHiF9Na7gD37+CokA13LPzHTb6UIcvG1qQ/W+YD5XuzkX8XAvflmjnJk9gJXEu7PiTB6pGs8ya"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18014","langCode":"en","question":"HqhdVn1SF33K8lSVso04982syNtR47+sW3uVVwPaRZ6oyz0v6wcgn7f5ewtqyfvnGZ/MgqmeFMlQFX955chqbg\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","who","when","whom"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14rnKqztzRrbOuE1I8sk+AlX7I1qbCKkVBAFRlVBWxLdC6ajWhEWcS85vs38xJh4ezB3fjTVRguUgWUwW5OwEDXjQG8+C+dKe3b/dYxFTKFSW3yyb5cs9HimuE8ZOKOkGRXYL2ppfC7DxlTE7dDhSpxlX2d4xjWWPv5WGX+bXTaB2M+wfyxTZMMETCA2Q/VppDYkSRRb/FdmYhg836zwNGkl+cLBL24guK79tPjN7AegV7BHi00BbbS1ZTOjdfOLK+pSSuscU4i3IQzCbVsTplglViMBg46zOonqOEezy3xDHzRa/q4JHWUr1KYhoLLovgoA1URNEJ+iDffm4MM6o69WE8IArPWPHc0WBT15B+Dah31KBLNRcF0cfYa/2sS7opmZKY88vSCXjVJGZYOFLscE8k43VMGzC20O9kFqTi9XEvmY8kZmXyaceil1aqLLvXTBhlkwedkvddx6ybK6HkxBPbD2B9gthyNq0nElWsf/CaqV4phFgZzZ188w0Jy8Cp0sNep4z7/5kP4In4vwvpcrN87mtmewUXFRqpZaPNuzLZcLy6v7ohwWDgM9ddaQ+OCfYw6RmxgWdzkH74LZeOsqB2cMIPXiFBwI6Iqn4CR9uSpe02Z7K6+hgXBD/oIW+wowUl3HAoon+if5ODrj73wQ1AOUao2F2bRiRj7fpJBKdtpr/dVKEk/gR4hfTWu4A9+/gqJANdyz8x02+lCHLxtakP1vmA+V7s5F/FwL35Zo5yZPYCVxLuz4kweqRrPMmg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18015","langCode":"en","question":"GrD5Rm0iiiayzvhbfVGf7VnYPqEE1uCbq9SXrlgrCq4dYMlM8RqpzXSwsPWMkOxY4/9p32IcDgC08v23r76vvQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["whose","which","whom","who"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14rnKqztzRrbOuE1I8sk+AlX7I1qbCKkVBAFRlVBWxLdNlytFkyJWAaHZQm2C1giHbm1e6ap7uyReWUw2Vagovt09UiuinCjdOP4OORUkPYXdFtFAEYmZghe/51Brll/keMvoSJkJGmXTrgnAherY//pmdob3VkQjiByY59cqJWxp8Tsh5Ii/QC1Wp5llfw50UoPOhd+Afj7KwWF7PFDUHzeOM6aUWeV3B4OKGa9RNwIb+jVy4sZVenAF4tww0DJvkbNNcXOZ6h6yGOTMVQx2OL2WwSBy8qqO6t4Y9UV5cQW1rOc1iC2XYM5osM5g3IM0Np4MV0VMjqQ5OR2zLwj7+A6DTVKHAEcPlpKWqBfsKWpmdIC2ci7ymo0YbuoPoqbq9+TxdspvNwNPpewvsoW9E5RNvfjYov6mNK25LFm5x6F6nAxjlwlyCXO0w8WPHht2zdhsx30f6lB1p2uO3q62/Vg9slbYEOqW8Ja8JDCuBtZiNLmZ/9HsbpmnORxqtcnIOw0bMWfvkfXCtHkbDO5NVFH+uEHDoQdGJorQcZp7h/xO1obD1gB9+rrkjizpqOL9tndCE7SRDT2wUmzwU0feDcYAGMpCYYl/BnmbWFz6A4tfmkYW9lTlytLRR6CInPQZuK9MMz77u6o7RjEXCxFflN2GjRx3pcdqNRnZOcPOvtdrYwSb8U1ZvFCFqd1c0+XiBtLscg8CAOHhxCXOebpbsRcM1bh/TM3y/3c/JzB0uhCwNGuU2YB4TwUXiLc0ScmYF5vlxqNudyzWpN+by3i6k9+6qlnOr76w5yFED79LeZg+jGZUSFmBDBvuea6tr1f5hjU+37lVD1KCs7AfM70DfosRqOHHTb1yQZeZMGGSrwMGT/AMnPR4RnNqi9efRwO/pOaOG9jqdZ8slr9eII7AoUBCDBejtvP6phJATkDsrHI"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18016","langCode":"en","question":"QUPt3NXrUVT9pR6uynlAOaQkBKG/Ljc5UEpagU/2E7nNTMX3eBM3Cv2LNDHMb90CjpECp3yC464SE8U+HDuPZg\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","who","whom","whose"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14rnKqztzRrbOuE1I8sk+AlX7I1qbCKkVBAFRlVBWxLdpxP2/h3oMPqhY0vVL/vg5AxmZBVvoVZNwNbwAj3ItgnYmxwXZGXdidQleVfKtCAcOC1/27FtGxCAw1mQfILt6NuNqducmCB5TQTwdygegsELpW0K4pd3126/s1HiJ86i1Y4QsN83L654bx+aJ6nlyWc25uvyJjGfILdPKQHgycHFZfzu8H7+Keu4PgqTT4gkNaQ6Ch+Y/6hWRQx2CHBq/0OjxifVXmiCj4Ijuvk0RyuJwg7oBvP/KyuCCBvCRQllw7T9QtDb0nt0JzCX9pyWBXqCfutHvGvAzV/8mAYn52MFmGqwKI+fAv3pzN0hBb1wT4rQG88au4rw+hr0WGT/8YNaG5sJe8O1cqYpV2wEYbEXibLEHwhcwEy4ttuJsFa3lUN+kZ7Fcf7yMH7WV5Gk9bivWkGsNUAHpfYO0Doqvz1vbQqljnpUTvqSxTD9MI5kjQWT8ZxoCvR0+D8YTAnPP5m7+Ne0PjIsl7v8soWgV1hucOBzTMhQEeIbKdG2yadkYqxE7teHKm7jNC+evOgImE4InfMb2EVy6qo9+sA/myJlJYsezTJQrZ5s9zr+AbkCdJ3g0d8YXUfb6bF4mpXPlpfB0pdGituy8Rxf77NnjcfM/WIsmmWm3gzwuQjYuUYbAngaGR+nNz48uJmSvPSCFYnp2AE+cdGPxzI3z4wAwGb5MlW2V4a6Ph5hbUkNjBe1yRib4igh+SCLxewM0kcMojh7N75/MX1Jq+UNk1+b1/9q+gvrQ4cLIMxXf2TfWHHkDKHYt3JWATARaQN6+r81N3/iztwmWPlEBTdRcWDjSELg1GS4djhGMrRK8z4WCUL+h31KBLNRcF0cfYa/2sS7opmZKY88vSCXjVJGZYOFLscE8k43VMGzC20O9kFqTi9XEvmY8kZmXyaceil1aqLLvXTBhlkwedkvddx6ybK6HkxBPbD2B9gthyNq0nElWsf/CaqV4phFgZzZ188w0Jy8Cmy6JjG7t3xOmqIy8Q0V29ip3mR+LELZ4RBEq0ZyeuhDs5BtVASVElafwvgBT8zifyL7NRYrlnos/v/LxSp61G0\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18017","langCode":"en","question":"uPPBzTp2UubDXK/99WtITgi0KPNYR5oM0W7YFzPdCTCH7xcS1QyiFWxFPGYbm/VilJZEG7ZTT/xR+5aW44bvNw\u003d\u003d","answers":["when","who","whom","in which"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x16Ef7FCvyaHJ6+renJ+LGOZaQhaNe0qZYLxcFsE0g8mMcKqm6GO5LkM1AnOkiJIxPm+EeW+Ems28dzJiLVzFe351ZsZU3pIClVo/TZxQ+/MADit9KboIySn0dNApOdn6P7nEWo6EnY2h9kNoHhCiMZeGrwfQmR8x1CYjmBamDK0ZWBha6mAk+kDG4Qs5783o+DXy9uhtkF9cDateS6zMqGTL4bkNRJ/BQnwFxupNq7HnAk67BPtMMAFxlGlF3PoQdLa+4uuoWVcc+NhZ2//fHGc008U9vNphCjx++KwaIvfwpONm17KI+4a+OfZ8h9xgzqO3PZmP/0TgMWK5C8sAynX/v7/0HPyBafg9IoycDQDyhSjZKWHwmImElLdQy03ujRdq4g9tjTeKyCLl7HhYR534VmMgO4U1Rge0FOAKrNBV+ywz8SldmEmIld7Euzl/rmeh4reVhZLrxrzARYV+Ty1zK/CD7zZOm6POyj9J5jzEuYufZeVY2dwgGBAh6hfbUSaBkjVoR5/6jRQ2bAGGu/W47PPqXyivq8kGWkQ2VK35i85oj4VWEgpklAeWvHW8yA2bkN1dRc34veOMt7UuUKkNOzvfd+2789nsh4jwi2qK9qlX2x6Y7rUi6LzF1/iru92X7Sr0RvVSkTkEVTgLiJKBCMobeZvyGz8/qOgpdrDC9muWbt0tMUeZw0hsVvrZZq/TziAAsDVTbeiUgbpBWHGxAPnWgXXg0ps0MmogHiX3/VTQJl7wf6I1LM2Yzrp1y77cqYadtnf/mkTTEwSuPxE7Nuu1UQZe+86jNbdbYksm6vY4tFhCwW+ao55zepcp6zZ5Cp5OHpl64em4w+L+NH27L+da7XYcc+kl7u5WAV76oYwp8OGKoFAfZ3LtzI3y5zh7N75/MX1Jq+UNk1+b1/8uelVp03wW54Ekr/kRh9ujCS3QE7FSoi0FwUOxneSDYy4akvYIgQeCJZAq4BQhny7DjzUH+vxRgiM5FA0U+GFutVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18018","langCode":"en","question":"29pYkOtmF3tJgM2A9oMz8p34+5lxyJqkDFYbKU9+6fDHR55or+4g7Dhh21/8Ssgjsh8DWgnO+E9uvgnO8I40Kg\u003d\u003d","answers":["whom","that","when","who"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1yuoGQHAN3NYD/PYbTi2W7QIXoM3wArK8rldrdFO+XCsz5hZ3kY6aMbV8VaBe23yumXJvpl/9ELLhJhqjJq/a8BTA/OMhYoswVUn1QTteXsiI2+c+mhbHVvQ5FKPTuzD/sqdFf1k6yoR4JS+aiZrlQQBmyfpF8S0aRSvg19SPSgzirb+xQVpjJjnNiSwSCLde2mxwGUXXZfVQULbzq60wF3T8MUnTQETQpZoq/EvsVkTojtcVhr9zxE9N3F8Gkh9ln4CvfLUbZHp4U1EXw09y+yUKWiNCZRcXTh0HwYxKBjr0M6UdYSXUJVEnf5IdOWJu+xaosVi7KMt2ijo/znY/YExnpn+uqDMAQRKVUCS3UJkSYa2aZfYEVSYbHEVNkpSZWQvlk3RjnYFe/yWtSdLhIapfMF7VD/tu14AHrKd8XmzY4d3mPc8sGtjQqtJLOPpODZ5Cp5OHpl64em4w+L+NH27L+da7XYcc+kl7u5WAV76oYwp8OGKoFAfZ3LtzI3y5zh7N75/MX1Jq+UNk1+b1/8uelVp03wW54Ekr/kRh9ujCS3QE7FSoi0FwUOxneSDYy4akvYIgQeCJZAq4BQhny7DjzUH+vxRgiM5FA0U+GFucLT4G/1GFkgRoG0lssycM0kUiq1byzB0M8tEHWsS1AiRIVFSc+J36pdA0WP3pqp0wqnVEwuhWlsuL5TfBWGSrB9PEeoUnbh9STYNADz36vQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18019","langCode":"en","question":"8XyFB+mEwfGocXc7QWMDPRWuYKBlLfOtzpL+lpmjGqZ+qTz8i3o8RQRLmh7ot6Xcx7QNyykEkTDQxxy9IkxxXcpenHkqTbK67aZWAcaL8yU3VEmZrgEZsuUbhCTF+xsCnxvenGhTt/NtPFF1d9hg0J603Jgj5YM0GRfAXg8Rj6FYbed9hldOVLqZWkJBwRaVTb6utti8IsfNCDIKXc27qQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["who","that","whose","where"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1yuoGQHAN3NYD/PYbTi2W7QIXoM3wArK8rldrdFO+XCsAG3lNVnkL2mkplB0m0ugGR4jVQJxbKe0vdYf8LDP5spLPzlKFES83/ciMptVMgSBGd/we+lu3olUtwkW4tlYRLXNYctBVF15BnbE/J/0VKMICcJJ/AWD/GrMCym1se+2n95gs2B/HGDpf6mBXh+HahhHH+eJAB5oHo6rOkYSEHz3HPwv/JDFvksHsAeKlOIQswBZVCCkqcdtw3cUuSkcNLRuVH0IZHnup8VAgfIsL/qLPj4BKSG4GKfjk6pk1KshU94H29hYTCIgS7UXEliUbZ8z+2JDuU9H1y5B/SdKs9L2WwSBy8qqO6t4Y9UV5cQWRkTCEvmamwkJAVpqK8YsC57AlHcuH9whlcEgnKmfvBhDl6hgdA+UE3fhANYk+02DgPtdstIiVm4aWkcWhRqutAvdktU7up4XPnWTHkhN0Cdn9qoeseKlpUsauYE3UrjgsWiq2IhYIMintDT87IMyEmQDkUZwz52C2hDObV+9CWGjInGEOM6DGrpOm8KCCuKveDRz+2db/4vmULvlrvAn+1RxbW0KgxPoXcjNEH7p1hQS/8QruAjXtOev5kNWTl5RM7F0ngvS2ibt4bfx+wtYcVDESJqXLTp8nQsU/l4S8e749Etan3t92L8mY8V6RLOH1VIg6fOF8s5Eugw7yBx1CzN2++ZMzap55zEoPYzS58g0dV9kuE9GC7NxHKHOwN86dLvrrNQuz6sPi2HypvilnvGUGAhSISn9NhApmc0qt0VkZW++3XBByLRf2A8iPYdyzitZQtb1bkbCOfKc8t3/jHrqWTUuSte4gGJO+SYySHKpaDX+Tvi2l1UNrSpYxG9lR5L8FMQEGWqCwSA8kMfL/GzFh/LxCts7rI/8+RxpmHrb54l7dDmCvisD6Yikcn8g"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18020","langCode":"en","question":"l5n+OpfgxExgHS5nLRdsVWBsIDdhvOXkvhUUAMiIlN0uL7WM6i/KPWc2CbgDR1W21Cx3VlpbtJG/vBO5/cl3Py4qaquurNLWJVSV14BnbZka2rMFbtWBH42fImCaHOdR","answers":["which","why","that","when"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1yuoGQHAN3NYD/PYbTi2W7QIXoM3wArK8rldrdFO+XCsDeSv+oD7eDeDNuuzpMOvzS9vWewid945S/qFRzjKZjFYOeo8dGkpHEl81AA8xb7b9lsEgcvKqjureGPVFeXEFm1AeFDX7pk3+Q1ekklhqUsda3wFXQsheBjRtcpoW0uqXw7C5nuca2kybV3JACZFxHHrPPt9BhY+tUuoBZ4u3jdMoRnLXEn3YgMmdyvwAwfmKhr9jxd2425lUeobp7y6F/9S1OkEVKt/Ms+Aalqo2eZ2VQqwUnoVCUMsckjuj1PzMYreeriB8hsNz5iSudQAeIqL6BO3r53bLmQdrVJxojHCQAB1SfsfgFANNCtJLp6c/hcmXM/LBZT9YPmt+gXARNA0cg+nO23F9gSazDGh7oQUGEtpRkEE0Nw33sNRJH6aU3rGh7AiDojIi8tHtJB7aJM/XObvRB9alorfdkxVPPhEZc9r+axVXCGXut7p+rEz+RprJnJvwv5bRLqAES7SU4yfYMSE3ZBFD07L9Tzf1xAN/n26WDvAU7v979Ys4UTSzkK9IPB/5QZLdfsMg7XFMD9KnT4pSLDFpornlRvMzlTsfbH2CYn2pqHtzmgWmGIWTDpL2zBh4/489a5bIo53PXc0w43NIoZSusT/xly8Dl7+mZSo8jrvJ+gxbj+RwphxbsIjTLWG5HmQ/PiQO8tjMXb++PhGX8oUHKYcjksYL6yvX4lxaK9rXKeuAIWr/0g/6wxV1M2MrTw4B3aMGKF+d1xNhcXd6YjmzpFQlG0d9CmEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18021","langCode":"en","question":"1QRtAyUAoyr1CvEwOG3+Qvj81gdbQz6cBBXlf0NoAA4QaiDyKx2zHm0VtGyxJ+OR","answers":["that","why","who","when"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1yuoGQHAN3NYD/PYbTi2W7QIXoM3wArK8rldrdFO+XCsBSGGdc8QqQq7GAx9SbIjSr/Y7UrdTneIpbSc/JuVgfC2exGLurxkpjo7oY9OIPJINGLQHZli/XWtqp3mPsBc5lF03Ch8ME4VWx14befQ6sYLvCitgmrP1zb94GFHn5ChSGl272CYadMcUHMT7A7V7Au/MbmyTX1YCySe+fYEiJ+aLXcz7KrWRpNoQI+tJwW6BEkPXWCyvzldXmgOfF1zl2BEQ9Kigh+jbxzAz7KtDuq8aEp2yBIsNyZJC3NsVr56ELcEYheJKEFH9XZNZEw11/apV9semO61Iui8xdf4q7vdl+0q9Eb1UpE5BFU4C4iSgQjKG3mb8hs/P6joKXawwvZrlm7dLTFHmcNIbFb62Wav084gALA1U23olIG6QVhx0sTodd8DKusgccShXcFxbYnp2AE+cdGPxzI3z4wAwGbs3gA2Y9b8sfCHq+ZE9o/l2WwTQssfFt8XIwejjaDBCx1C81Oe1gxrB0sV0Nq0l1U+PtHO0QYoGv5IDx0q4/L5cbFZe9rqTmhwNmkKwsZdmkzsR3HX5nkR9gTKpcaPpJYDA97Q/pg9lAOzy38m5srXE44nxpPTms/3cwyntFKFrVRmAt4OV6VBGX1i0xo06guJIiPyzkMDohRR8Tx0Ls6Uyvrh402wKCNdRtNJj+JMsRx+nkz+m6lYHyQuU++fVdQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18022","langCode":"en","question":"LLycZeiyjRMicaatvhFwamGgFKnbsFPa8gv5v+h7Rer92qfJyh1MnLATnvUp20Fk","answers":["whose","where","that","who"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1yuoGQHAN3NYD/PYbTi2W7QN6MAygtPUGWKi7gfh1swo6NICyIoXuIfbw5kQ1OSe7nhBFjeDpn25yzfON2cz5eCFHyibF+3SGrZDjsEYKLVBb1/Qd7pYveBIyzPTdoUQ0MKt9DqxuIfTmOe+eTl2LAZ+Ic1tx87+QgczdDTH4BsgaxJpjSK8MlOyxvihOzo8Qd6UI+CsRj/vR/P4069adquYQUDUf5rEdx6+kDKVWr87saT2K/dnRH4NVeaerhXp446eXZUQOmQjui3N9TNHlERCecZG9sq1eliKHzbTql0joEThfVMNHA8o4/3A80UwIexaosVi7KMt2ijo/znY/YExnpn+uqDMAQRKVUCS3UJkSYa2aZfYEVSYbHEVNkpSZWQvlk3RjnYFe/yWtSdLhIapfMF7VD/tu14AHrKd8XmzY4d3mPc8sGtjQqtJLOPpOBuT0DeDxYaLkuEV1emKaLShRjOGqTNhZ5dEKk9IWnf/1ZeQHIXPbV6P18zEX+UzJnrqWTUuSte4gGJO+SYySHKq5cNGNbQ3IlUMfWr+0lUxN1AM+GiNGS60vJBed3HjP0VrpzfhQuvhOuU+tZPDgUMbyRskPsB3ZCWcxkgrGWtKyiTvBl3hjoPuWk338vOpgkBAufMZTKz+K2vpuOcGf+Sg9UkXaJOeMjW33xEGFE+8BdTsqioIPoYytnw8K5Ar72HmnugcKiTmP9/KHCPrciR/jRX3MkOfY9nXpkrhNyhwXjXUJ4XxAhY+ehvFOwtecsKc+qJmZc24OKrdXwdYx1osXmb0ykea7NYkKNSTaMClC/BFc+82Utlb4SxPAlWl/x1C81Oe1gxrB0sV0Nq0l1WnF8HhWbfx6f6VTdKX0pQcIlk1PmK59SnORbLNLBBXyh7d9gY73GDhArGy5iVSarTPiCDuMGQzxDwfGKb8q1C8"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18023","langCode":"en","question":"GDummnIw2hyKI+niC8Q6clV9RlQB0epiIXrOip97DhqWCEM0Qp6cgvJGVc+QTCjHgVGYNb7nSS7V2ghoDhgxJg\u003d\u003d","answers":["who","that","where","whose"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1yuoGQHAN3NYD/PYbTi2W7QIXoM3wArK8rldrdFO+XCs4/uZ/oeRLlQSyqvovaBT8zMgBwUQV7vYUBtJ6oBoN5pLwFKJJiZ4FGaA80+Y+wK0gyLLEiCO7wJ1T6J5ds7SlcRSlfM/EIxBQV7V485a81No+i9iCJiidfbYNjl0FVgzC013xF/Nbel8Vu42KFRAd6+bpm1Q13qS0+yPeDjuusL2dITPX0kcK5MAydNWiM/1J6EDhs6EgJloKNVH1ryjOl29uHMVupkFAgglb6+V95oVPhDxmhAH6XbYWi2PzLaGRpU7qjVRkDWUIvdIid0N2ZnSAtnIu8pqNGG7qD6Km6vfk8XbKbzcDT6XsL7KFvROUTb342KL+pjStuSxZucehTNP6PAqvfPYg4GFcbEBJpSCP19Rf+98gw1jbYOfj9y1dMAb6dHiGAH3FhncpWHkqxZIeKRbPeTC1EvQdG1Q9SwUpKIhEkOWOCeOcLzIBKi1wGsxwoodmDIvFn42ZU3WEYmceFDO6sX4IHBOGNXZfQaAWKzTIusEtjNITwUW2US6mhFpIXkxdYyM4LupYh6DoZZLl4LGxoJDGM8ZgCnS5MGTbjvg6CSZRmWzcfaTrh/FxNFTrvls+kAEKKhO1jR061oNYqPIQkwAYKFEu3kuWKGtxD1nCxYdLBJc/VwyUupehixFEdb8IcIYTe2kHNMm/6xSoe90AMC5487cyeBIeSOu2zA0NYFFPoPQlPjsxj7keR37fYc7aqdwPTXYv15mj3sGMpTaE8b+2D+AB/5Tg9ssjSooC/xSdclCmslbqQPTlRTsRiF6hcQMgJgWNREaEcKSu/5NwhMJFHPAOVu7JGe/bscIErDdIjEnJUMmfGyWC9iqvJy8twRqCmedF0Rqv7QJjwCDxC9/ttsVsFAE7ejfdXG16pGVqPiPdcYPcZI5"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18024","langCode":"en","question":"XMYKkfqxt9uFXgm3HcXJkzlSfLBfAlhx9641uUvDPy0xJeNifkEgAZ5cXa94gh4VzBuEdOsQpLeb92jDQwM5H4tqTWGs0qTS2pvBJNnWJlY\u003d","answers":["where","who","whom","whose"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14tysGYiYZHCt/iKhLiZZX+mGumVmzpZKuv8XWh9/v7DG6oLPZ2axF7VQmqeWD71l99F32P2kTl13JKqWsVEaNR0yucrNO7KxjNTaMidNFasGABjKQmGJfwZ5m1hc+gOLX5pGFvZU5crS0UegiJz0GbivTDM++7uqO0YxFwsRX5Tdho0cd6XHajUZ2TnDzr7Xa2MEm/FNWbxQhandXNPl4gbS7HIPAgDh4cQlznm6W7EXDNW4f0zN8v93PycwdLoQsDRrlNmAeE8FF4i3NEnJmBeb5cajbncs1qTfm8t4upPfuqpZzq++sOchRA+/S3mYPoxmVEhZgQwb7nmura9X+YY1Pt+5VQ9SgrOwHzO9A36LEajhx029ckGXmTBhkq8DBk/wDJz0eEZzaovXn0cDv6TmjhvY6nWfLJa/XiCOwKFCIv7Y4BpsdUft/fRKqly6XgQzK3ptja4O73MCrUBGSh1U2oX3bXbZJkDU2dhri7JM9eg2JAfkeRR9X6PFeexrGom1Jo7X7r1o95GGl5J/YcL3ZLVO7qeFz51kx5ITdAnZ/aqHrHipaVLGrmBN1K44LFoqtiIWCDIp7Q0/OyDMhJkA5FGcM+dgtoQzm1fvQlhoyJxhDjOgxq6TpvCggrir3g0c/tnW/+L5lC75a7wJ/uGWPe2+NGvhEliGdzLX13ZGH/gXPD0SE1ffXZtJlvsbHUyJ62TOYHEd4G5hQqIihSb1u7/1LomAVq+hdy2yGj0qd5kfixC2eEQRKtGcnroQ7OQbVQElRJWn8L4AU/M4n8i+zUWK5Z6LP7/y8UqetRt"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18025","langCode":"en","question":"8F4+1J1nM2gA9GD0fpJenQ+/mCGeLmp5H+WwXDy2pq2uAHWigO5c7okmNDW3pu6UF6+l56v5f8tpVmquzqZZ3A\u003d\u003d","answers":["who","which","whom","whose"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14tysGYiYZHCt/iKhLiZZX90OAke1TH6Ywi/6HeEysKtxJXT8SQ/MWoPchFaPGZ9RiELcM0L0a6rN6oNWmt7AarP5KQjzbqMMmM7WDY4IS0U4rQPrLQbtgNdbaAXD2oH4ey1zfjeAJ5ssSvaYbKu5uWMsON86LDdEI51PLDDlO5z9lsEgcvKqjureGPVFeXEFjrNcjqwFIeuhhT32UdBo1PVDgkUl/LilVnEtJNdRMo74U8Fn88vmAeSYAp9FkWP0auJtRq+8cL0mvGBtOlTQ74UpKIhEkOWOCeOcLzIBKi1kZquSuPz+3mCqnMG6ttx2AowUl3HAoon+if5ODrj73y61iI7NxXeTpOv+bOQ5zaikPJKhsqdmzDc0BaqCaxIsYjJY8kEkDMU7lqA6uZIYXc4K7Y0D5EMC6IfGDQPw9RBrK7j8WFObn11ZD7o2/T9xNVSIOnzhfLORLoMO8gcdQtwDFAD0xeRNKYOcz77ub8dJgbSYDqaLPk6Ye/6sbLYlHRTyhit81Nx/jP9AIQc3+enhBhpCboKPycLzcBlSdTkhZVHxWF53CEM7+7N/30jC37HhAi0bGqnKZ/CAOYQy8Juwqz4+shR8o4LjWC1/+5/eCIPVfSVIztPBD15MLY1yfmuqWp/A7dfLonaz0IT5txgUdoGkkFkW9r0sveTlJzPDDmUXUvpbbaFqQS0PPPh9upItn4gEOBeHxrtyT7nCB2PjhLpXCbf3c5QC2XxdO5bi9IyABdbK9lRBu5kpQUZ9IRwF1GvJ495uduzSe2jnopk0rQmx7soGXYuH+NnhaUZHrGxSHy+P8lGYcvIkU9gjYp3snGbANiv16rglVMEcK0\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18026","langCode":"en","question":"ruBhShZvawC7go6mRkOprqD20fhrTx3NNdlNxjCwxtXnQs7Ggj+NuD0rt6EbbMampcN8RpRkagIow3ybkqGU8XUBZKAjEGu9g0ss08Yzg6WRTwiXMXBwCcLpmySEalqX","answers":["who","when","which","whose"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14tysGYiYZHCt/iKhLiZZX8nh5eKbwAN8zJFE/kCg/C4a8orFFHgDZOjSBpCjdDtVD1BZ/hU7v/ybBXui18d4Ifv01G51QQcDI/Il4MHmu9x/9GiAGoJEeIwTT9iYiroYxi66Sq07+a/R5EKFyhqzzuQ+Jtcre2It1+Ur/gPQFkjf/M3CgYERyAW+RHv1lYQaEqwWkCv+pGIYZKhYAFPS86e7zA1Z0z/gGxxviZ+9r6zXDFJPfJxT5pEjywVRx6TiHI7iv+MuAeBhjYSrpGP29ymUCu9kkJOsQGruK8GQ9BOtK86kCqk84lV1Moc56crRMDol9rooKl1JMW2k2yQ2DT/Xco6tsNh1zMGbKhHOZ96nCIWYDahtdJpu5Iu4s9iRD3P5TQ2l+7aA+klFvGPHVqbgo7IzYEm0YL574UKYx7MLvI9l9+GOP1XJLszNAJR9JLVHZTQj4O+ApDpxZvUGwqlT1Wxx+/CT5RdFEMsHGHHEu1B/ryH0p+s45UEQ7DJIcrhVMUczkafPXBC2f9rIoe0cEkPvABcYDzrmJmGdxdxIbAUpRUOMWC8G/zlwoGDm10+JPpXB4eSHxUgeoAigMyvwxsYxvUaGv40QqSFlnb9uy0RLfiVl0lKzrFbxmJ2WRfTdN/V9Buxr/upoHQ/6a7j3Hq15yqYaMksLEDp39pofgDxrR33AQG1dxkudg2bbAadCFHCsHkkKERDJX+axjwiIGLvBoyvaU9pV5c5F21tN1RugQYX+cAJbWjXubNnxKaSrMZ1r4p/zH8t+x22Vy5vtkPX8jfX3KTNLXvaqP3iTy7RIXoz1vsoa/v2nhcKjSsGHTqWYVLMmWjZucIq/DbOl0SXz1GU4AFxi6vFuMuKArbfXnBRlj/4rIGasSoFN9fAwq/TvhaLKJ5jj1EyLZ66ezlazXXe6hjIv8i9PGx9"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18027","langCode":"en","question":"nSVfRAyDfI1DoYuFb+qf7fcq4CmAyPNXCrWuwarPD2B5UfDOZBK055XxaXk+sA3MOQyUbXjEv1nlku/2UKQ0XezRuKfmRg9dAocq2HidZaVNoTOGV+aTBKQggtCERaTt","answers":["why","whose","when","whom"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14tysGYiYZHCt/iKhLiZZX8nh5eKbwAN8zJFE/kCg/C4beGxnCrRi20XMmiEedVIktRvbRAtTn2oAymi5OnUJ2TaAaHAqOD/d/WQ62Lu8Q/c+KpB8ApZKYCN9JEtcrbFK8A7f5Oca1Su9vGXm+ijiIq7y/apQxza25Xwg4cgvSfIhA4oRPrTJJ7N1OxRX3A+9sgTaJY8GFHM08vo6ePgVBdg+GI+KGfwaWO7RwSGY8Cn2tKFNWuos3pIUOXxTvfkjyzCr1iUmAMLd9LyaLQH22YsHiq+e6ykBgrOC6PVdmp8l3nVjEfF/g7hDWguS/KH5tyzRMXYfN5aD2+tWlbS2+Jdrb5SuN02aCYnromclpMFVtN5N+9YQD9hcKil/hfXhiQj7jnw/Uv/klfMqsgRXxL/zr4q4LiP/Az7m0pbaY2M8fRrM3YS5HM+m+C5ZFj8k/9heyD5bYOLZGNd5hFl7RtXnlhW3nJgV/VRRApG/s2szOUAQkZQfWprjHTSjRn1uUcVqU+7geypQweCOA0swRW27yQeivP1+12cLIrrjD+wBoJBiisVVAe9xQElb1ytAniR3reDp+eQAdReL9bOjsZHMpUm8R1A9F1jzYFDOVRrFOtX7/qnfSOfcJ2XGBpMD320ge6IDUQnYrq6qJI3iSkiKq8MOFXURMWEXLIYrR9CGNT7fuVUPUoKzsB8zvQN+oKYne1kp6zvJ2hzjMEcTGIp1yHbCCAuNaVrBKXipPdClxOn538a8pPn8esofv1ybVK84Nfk/w4FfkTa6UF9+tpipUZyHPxuIEt/U0x4VMPO"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18028","langCode":"en","question":"dEdp7M0Rwdln3yhr3ARlidlQMpBBwmB0y1F0ehiP1IYP9vrtqjcd32BwuoDgjUZqcP9gWgle0vLylBhRs+RpTuhwPqfNKV2hgATXfkUBE+E\u003d","answers":["why","where","whose","who"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14tysGYiYZHCt/iKhLiZZX8nh5eKbwAN8zJFE/kCg/C4sOzyM/b/niV8cdlmKUeb9lCKUYOt+JfrH0VsJu45SGLaAaHAqOD/d/WQ62Lu8Q/c+KpB8ApZKYCN9JEtcrbFK8A7f5Oca1Su9vGXm+ijiIq7y/apQxza25Xwg4cgvSfIhA4oRPrTJJ7N1OxRX3A+9sgTaJY8GFHM08vo6ePgVBdg+GI+KGfwaWO7RwSGY8Cn2tKFNWuos3pIUOXxTvfkjyzCr1iUmAMLd9LyaLQH22YsHiq+e6ykBgrOC6PVdmp8l3nVjEfF/g7hDWguS/KH5tyzRMXYfN5aD2+tWlbS2+Jdrb5SuN02aCYnromclpMFVtN5N+9YQD9hcKil/hfXhiQj7jnw/Uv/klfMqsgRXxL/zr4q4LiP/Az7m0pbaY2MnZe9mpebWmy3HLvkrJGTsR87JkE7021cnNzW2YqlHYAOOMJ04j2wayNv2Zod8CqW+0wPut141ds3ZVdBt41/+1t9jBc6MPefFYUFp4a0F9M7Pw0TdSf1ra+UiSqFGj0Xdc63X7HRVhILBAoQmL06IHsGMpTaE8b+2D+AB/5Tg9t6VMrCRte4fVYhCvlypO2o0JlSJjQN2DFb7i7RYobsTtzmr6q0oehy9D7Ts0j42F4SUvkA9Tp+eQXUxuSzjqOYg76mkmRUrWoR6zWTXSNckqo6a3f3RFCwGBvbeSoxcaBNgdA5Y+xUbhsePEJlx30aDwzMZ5MwyLPb6erUGnUcInuGNCrevP9/DDXvKQa1b+0GGvEVir3/pC8B0EUhJhio"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18029","langCode":"en","question":"kc96HBK7lnC2u9JUJ9gIEdnuaCTXunUYKN5a4q1f9it1BozVs7Sj/1OOHwb7hyinvXQ+iz1UuLfF3dkgztETUw\u003d\u003d","answers":["when","whose","whom","which"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14tysGYiYZHCt/iKhLiZZX+k2MtQX13lCTGq3hf4bdCc+ie7C8IY2MjtbIQbHevfFwrNfw054rGXlcC6Tzqd+PvaAaHAqOD/d/WQ62Lu8Q/c+KpB8ApZKYCN9JEtcrbFK8A7f5Oca1Su9vGXm+ijiIq7y/apQxza25Xwg4cgvSfIhA4oRPrTJJ7N1OxRX3A+9sgTaJY8GFHM08vo6ePgVBdg+GI+KGfwaWO7RwSGY8Cn2tKFNWuos3pIUOXxTvfkjyzCr1iUmAMLd9LyaLQH22YsHiq+e6ykBgrOC6PVdmp8l3nVjEfF/g7hDWguS/KH5tyzRMXYfN5aD2+tWlbS2+Jdrb5SuN02aCYnromclpMFVtN5N+9YQD9hcKil/hfXhiQj7jnw/Uv/klfMqsgRXxL/zr4q4LiP/Az7m0pbaY2M8fRrM3YS5HM+m+C5ZFj8k/9heyD5bYOLZGNd5hFl7RtXnlhW3nJgV/VRRApG/s2szOUAQkZQfWprjHTSjRn1uXubo2vqpYEcZSrM6R4mDnv81WgxX9no+eJypZc/t5wAJ20EklgyyEN+czYxx+w3UG6G5b7siFhxTIFLQ13pO/7qxS6ZakhMFDNsm5XG6KrEnhpNStK8PEwJ5TPj3Ox4IKNMN8CDwtSQfSYr7gOsS4pNc7Ydf9XQNKMu2oUz8WQGTusMCFWfP/6K9iCTAL5Wus6bnZiFPuqWL5lvidrNfREaVsEyuxHjfwMUkgirPnb7K5f+QPagDClg+O3Sn8G2+rH7nJsLKh4hgKfg7dggYOqJnHhQzurF+CBwThjV2X0GFpXm7Bq1sG9GVcBOYIL972uNIcRTvq5ZkO7kBGwXopyzhoXMXmyVBXt3cv9qpoyYGxqEUBrLTb4DrlSFnse6mIRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18030","langCode":"en","question":"dZTyMi43ol7bEHZV6etAyTBe49CFY3JcdqlQ3K5b/lYChpNj0WL5ZYRJU/97O6ho18zeKd6fDto0IX0z1EbyxA\u003d\u003d","answers":["who","whom","when","why"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17o4T4HXMYM2xHdtA2AAQHWqwme/xfYKU8yuC1UOooDmaERni1mfTMiyjMkNsN4KBlAj0YBmuxTj5edkyUl/NxoL2sY8jn0OsQiYnGlVhFLtaF11rvxLk326tqmqHsNrI1Vy47XX9bpKbInwDJmPxXXHh+ruR7kO/3pCVvS442dDxJns2eqEC0H5vi/XW8ih8QtXwK8uwQowjJZjNy2KV8RxtncCd/cHh7/V6HCH51T2pK9dPugQ4TRVZkYoPZ3N8O455B6fIyRm8rWzkhgrjCmuNpQ1GTNzFpAQ7TTVul7mWK9WxzNXZxE/KGfNRzzRn4cO/eL8m/zSau6GWJl0ate7IMZfBknROqsOtQ3xyTF9rK7j8WFObn11ZD7o2/T9xNVSIOnzhfLORLoMO8gcdQtwDFAD0xeRNKYOcz77ub8dJgbSYDqaLPk6Ye/6sbLYlHRTyhit81Nx/jP9AIQc3+enhBhpCboKPycLzcBlSdTkhZVHxWF53CEM7+7N/30jC37HhAi0bGqnKZ/CAOYQy8Juwqz4+shR8o4LjWC1/+5/eCIPVfSVIztPBD15MLY1yS8vSntRGZSCb8RLNVz5Q9p+uy/ijbraXNG3OFEvyMhGMj8k/e2zSA/pyCaymeCOraPAXmaAmDJpC5cWXKh1WjNmD4ZMdHZJXWF5peI5vl9SdZEwjxW0+VCwI2DieroRA06uMGpqjFOo6rKnUStOH07EnrxMNzhB2Vx9BjGXnQV5NMjA6ikRvsbQ0EIqgxJmLg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18031","langCode":"en","question":"lf356DYpg2/IxRAZp/tUiQlVLFIf6tuuy0ypPFclRO1SeZVXRp8g9T2ghgGusKBJOit3eUx5EZFPokt8X5m3d9EKQzJS5sjiSzkX2bquMLE\u003d","answers":["where","whom","why","whose"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17o4T4HXMYM2xHdtA2AAQHWqwme/xfYKU8yuC1UOooDmaERni1mfTMiyjMkNsN4KBlAj0YBmuxTj5edkyUl/NxoL2sY8jn0OsQiYnGlVhFLtaF11rvxLk326tqmqHsNrI1Vy47XX9bpKbInwDJmPxXXHh+ruR7kO/3pCVvS442dDxJns2eqEC0H5vi/XW8ih8QtXwK8uwQowjJZjNy2KV8RxtncCd/cHh7/V6HCH51T2pK9dPugQ4TRVZkYoPZ3N8O455B6fIyRm8rWzkhgrjCmuNpQ1GTNzFpAQ7TTVul7mWK9WxzNXZxE/KGfNRzzRn4cO/eL8m/zSau6GWJl0ate7IMZfBknROqsOtQ3xyTF9xWkmFmz+LIZHY8aWYHaPs8tt7SlkjO1yQhe+04xY7s4aW06+tR4VldeBMmenTkGLUh0mW+0qUHloT2cvbJDH+ZZLl4LGxoJDGM8ZgCnS5MGTbjvg6CSZRmWzcfaTrh/FxNFTrvls+kAEKKhO1jR061oNYqPIQkwAYKFEu3kuWKGtxD1nCxYdLBJc/VwyUupehixFEdb8IcIYTe2kHNMm/6xSoe90AMC5487cyeBIeSOu2zA0NYFFPoPQlPjsxj7keR37fYc7aqdwPTXYv15mj3sGMpTaE8b+2D+AB/5Tg9ssjSooC/xSdclCmslbqQPTlRTsRiF6hcQMgJgWNREaEcKSu/5NwhMJFHPAOVu7JGe/bscIErDdIjEnJUMmfGyWC9iqvJy8twRqCmedF0Rqv7QJjwCDxC9/ttsVsFAE7ejgQ8k8BQUEDsfZiBxYudiNewYylNoTxv7YP4AH/lOD23pUysJG17h9ViEK+XKk7ajQmVImNA3YMVvuLtFihuxO3OavqrSh6HL0PtOzSPjYXhJS+QD1On55BdTG5LOOo5jbRCGfXCEKYwDcLGT8DBXt"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18032","langCode":"en","question":"PrlwwXD/tb3kqbxjwCa9MtYIfzuo09xkYOfiXM2VfUVKXLnYMTjGJhq9rK0eJ75kLXcQFg2Oyq7yMIMz2fGe4w\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","who","why","when"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17o4T4HXMYM2xHdtA2AAQHWqwme/xfYKU8yuC1UOooDmaERni1mfTMiyjMkNsN4KBlAj0YBmuxTj5edkyUl/NxoL2sY8jn0OsQiYnGlVhFLtaF11rvxLk326tqmqHsNrI1Vy47XX9bpKbInwDJmPxXXHh+ruR7kO/3pCVvS442dDxJns2eqEC0H5vi/XW8ih8QtXwK8uwQowjJZjNy2KV8RxtncCd/cHh7/V6HCH51T2pK9dPugQ4TRVZkYoPZ3N8O455B6fIyRm8rWzkhgrjCmuNpQ1GTNzFpAQ7TTVul7mWK9WxzNXZxE/KGfNRzzRn4cO/eL8m/zSau6GWJl0ate7IMZfBknROqsOtQ3xyTF9rK7j8WFObn11ZD7o2/T9xNVSIOnzhfLORLoMO8gcdQtwDFAD0xeRNKYOcz77ub8dJgbSYDqaLPk6Ye/6sbLYlHRTyhit81Nx/jP9AIQc3+enhBhpCboKPycLzcBlSdTk1U2D4pN/64ECqkcPMniI0PZ3fWZYHK6O27g+h2OfeZBvKkYTYhUukp7pqcY9l7R0euLsjANd6fwyXYXGW88mOzvamfW9DTVt0V+b43VhJ5c95q/OUpQtIv1w45gns2iget1XS1WQDgk9MSlb9fDGfLysK2lebRmFvZFwPacGLY7Fyq6Y2z3VyYX81UgUUKA8w1kZEB32cri7hF13f92g+XI7iv+MuAeBhjYSrpGP29z0No+EEMVHPwDqqIBMOEV3n0rsKekMePe6xbADVvkjlsKSu/5NwhMJFHPAOVu7JGcv0UCQjeO9uo6qb8wK7ez4zlXqfESeEDFJULqOMcHvvflYwEGKZj2DEz4fW/5XPvav2p0c6fMKvIEGDftKidb8"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18033","langCode":"en","question":"zo5X2m2KPRI0P4HHLs84Q9LnjCfszBWn6jWvia4/Te7+OvHt5r1dmGOxcK9W3iWz","answers":["where","which","whom","who"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1w28Zbwcl93z9kzwuOJmV/pj6/+AaBnQOxdhS/5jroqFptCfqlwFBctt9SL3RGL14rF58EBHgoKrcbvS3vxejQAUpKIhEkOWOCeOcLzIBKi1wGsxwoodmDIvFn42ZU3WEYmceFDO6sX4IHBOGNXZfQaAWKzTIusEtjNITwUW2US69Di/p2Thnze7ZTrcIhdTKc6gzlmFseimfNcZcpBXIb9yHndWTcgZo/jvPadjkh90CCWr6ON3rn+gcCmkhvnVxooj9gqpCzWkqA9Esw/m94GsruPxYU5ufXVkPujb9P3E1VIg6fOF8s5Eugw7yBx1C3AMUAPTF5E0pg5zPvu5vx0mBtJgOpos+Tph7/qxstiUdFPKGK3zU3H+M/0AhBzf56eEGGkJugo/JwvNwGVJ1OSFlUfFYXncIQzv7s3/fSMLfseECLRsaqcpn8IA5hDLwm7CrPj6yFHyjguNYLX/7n94Ig9V9JUjO08EPXkwtjXJ+a6pan8Dt18uidrPQhPm3GBR2gaSQWRb2vSy95OUnM8MOZRdS+lttoWpBLQ88+H26ki2fiAQ4F4fGu3JPucIHY+OEulcJt/dzlALZfF07luL0jIAF1sr2VEG7mSlBRn0hHAXUa8nj3m527NJ7aOeimTStCbHuygZdi4f42eFpRkesbFIfL4/yUZhy8iRT2CNineycZsA2K/XquCVUwRwrQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18034","langCode":"en","question":"vR9jwEXbhE3qBPtymYU2rZUghy1uO6SzUNH1i2d/SB4UQhVzpWUEIjocKhJK2RAQDRYOSp4xKxxyh8BBHIlf+Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["where","whose","whom","who"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1w28Zbwcl93z9kzwuOJmV/pj6/+AaBnQOxdhS/5jroqFNIoKGyTXVAGGU0f8tDep7LF58EBHgoKrcbvS3vxejQAUpKIhEkOWOCeOcLzIBKi1wGsxwoodmDIvFn42ZU3WEYmceFDO6sX4IHBOGNXZfQaAWKzTIusEtjNITwUW2US69Di/p2Thnze7ZTrcIhdTKc6gzlmFseimfNcZcpBXIb9yHndWTcgZo/jvPadjkh90CCWr6ON3rn+gcCmkhvnVxooj9gqpCzWkqA9Esw/m94F265fSvYUFgs34LNcdWr3irf/vILjgYhGtQP6azJ75kqKcDxMtYsstjRFvmowPdBostAsrFtqM4CWNvo/p/0Dk51OD4UdvRLxn9gY3Ap/MeeiIkuQMV+opD/OE9ZPL5vGkGhu3e5AeBuFzKfU/s56WFfz367QwGGe2khErJLkkzFHd7a0ufHP4iYZFuvUA6y1n9qoeseKlpUsauYE3UrjgsAdcjo1dgPNzf3o21tGaNEmFuJ0z2IlL7CNVSW+WQJHGDJcnf0PPMhJJAAMavV2m0Gg+sj+4Wx3PRRdu0mnXj5/1WRRSCQYmX/01icToMVhGuToHdZyaPgGNNHsnXTgi8fRrM3YS5HM+m+C5ZFj8k/9heyD5bYOLZGNd5hFl7RtXnlhW3nJgV/VRRApG/s2szOUAQkZQfWprjHTSjRn1uYWE53OsPx3NFx6DO1Mv0RC0qMJJOyrmZvkLimSuc2mrCeh1IL3BFtLMz9OPVgiG/hTAHFG+x57gouPmFjPUEQrj8VMB28Zj8sS2ggdNm6N8Q5eoYHQPlBN34QDWJPtNg4pA3DTAZF5riSc0Sv26ayU\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18035","langCode":"en","question":"3yE4/I20srn3lE/5Terl+umHsNB+KjT0XMd73JT9fo1TcG+vc4IN6idwAhTMKjLe+9FFu1Q+PN58GMn1v/gujsO2uNkIH7lUvTT10ntdQkw\u003d","answers":["where","which","whose","who"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1w28Zbwcl93z9kzwuOJmV/pj6/+AaBnQOxdhS/5jroqFptCfqlwFBctt9SL3RGL14rF58EBHgoKrcbvS3vxejQAUpKIhEkOWOCeOcLzIBKi1wGsxwoodmDIvFn42ZU3WEYmceFDO6sX4IHBOGNXZfQaAWKzTIusEtjNITwUW2US69Di/p2Thnze7ZTrcIhdTKc6gzlmFseimfNcZcpBXIb9yHndWTcgZo/jvPadjkh90CCWr6ON3rn+gcCmkhvnVxooj9gqpCzWkqA9Esw/m94GsruPxYU5ufXVkPujb9P3E1VIg6fOF8s5Eugw7yBx1C3AMUAPTF5E0pg5zPvu5vx1tA9t28sJ9QUWfxu+DM3SO9muWbt0tMUeZw0hsVvrZZq/TziAAsDVTbeiUgbpBWHGn7vK3XIfoslnBy8kgS6hbiCPjQukbqo9uwmFl68hsF3T1SK6KcKN04/g45FSQ9hd0W0UARiZmCF7/nUGuWX+R4y+hImQkaZdOuCcCF6tj/+mZ2hvdWRCOIHJjn1yolbGnxOyHkiL9ALVanmWV/DnRSg86F34B+PsrBYXs8UNQfN44zppRZ5XcHg4oZr1E3Ag0M+j7415EWo24jcBYK0qNRWunN+FC6+E65T61k8OBQxvJGyQ+wHdkJZzGSCsZa0rKJO8GXeGOg+5aTffy86mCQEC58xlMrP4ra+m45wZ/5KD1SRdok54yNbffEQYUT7wF1OyqKgg+hjK2fDwrkCvvYeae6BwqJOY/38ocI+tyJH+NFfcyQ59j2demSuE3KHBeNdQnhfECFj56G8U7C15ywpz6omZlzbg4qt1fB1jHWixeZvTKR5rs1iQo1JNowKUL8EVz7zZS2VvhLE8CVaX/HULzU57WDGsHSxXQ2rSXVacXweFZt/Hp/pVN0pfSlBwiWTU+Yrn1Kc5Fss0sEFfKHt32BjvcYOECsbLmJVJqtMeOpR3r/nS9cdCSbfzkUZU\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18036","langCode":"en","question":"V4zvTHaVD24zGZWmOrtcs2LJ8v0a4s7/xhgglO0sDe1bvxbwLhRBxkAbcKRGPw7QAheFfnm2wDIT3NlzARtubQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["who","when","why","where"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1w28Zbwcl93z9kzwuOJmV/pj6/+AaBnQOxdhS/5jroqFNdzV5S+PcRCM3FajLfRl/K0M+cVUeIXdkZJqeEiRZohHKBNpgpd+MEtFJNvqLMnJYtyTQwk+wnszLQ7rbIw6s2ERrbfNIWVr5I8jomMNqZBr9fo1Y/g1o4QKzVGD4Bu161rIlahDQ1RcDaA/8ySKuhYr3Q01FYqyevS8GiKhze3qf0a4zXCTDMMjATsVZhsz8cqiGW674e7tiskUFw8Ydeo3beVEJ6FWQQrv9xIu5xZ8r3d7TSsWMk6SQo4zUnFS/muGL3moCg7tOgo7wcLLYuzgT+Oi2QHVYNi6d6CNJIiaMircX6CZt+v8AVawgtcj1los98wZm+SoRsK2QjQo5qCNiN6k9bn953pLa9Tj8nX/qoPDHbc34mGui5fvBHXfcjuK/4y4B4GGNhKukY/b3PQ2j4QQxUc/AOqogEw4RXefSuwp6Qx497rFsANW+SOWwpK7/k3CEwkUc8A5W7skZy/RQJCN4726jqpvzArt7PjOVep8RJ4QMUlQuo4xwe+9+VjAQYpmPYMTPh9b/lc+9let2/rF0iPIYL7nacc/CnagIzX57LvIWXGMfZVQ2yTL2pOK4aUX+bU7kVN2EMlA6bWjfbSC+kutREYQaIJQT4wLRrj8M20QPh6YZ+ugY2aZvPmhYlQkqwb17Q3ekYKqtA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18037","langCode":"en","question":"yUL4NEOgYLOBJVW7sfqFUeoWH4TYwMBSMbTp/nO4/UkHQ1YNYExVjgXpTBPVuxNi5wv0FK2oeKmLpcuhOq6qSQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["who","whose","in which","whom"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x16Ef7FCvyaHJ6+renJ+LGOYKWdOHp93nKaVYV6cLiJliL1bFIxf5KwaZKQjchfKBOLF58EBHgoKrcbvS3vxejQAUpKIhEkOWOCeOcLzIBKi1wGsxwoodmDIvFn42ZU3WEYmceFDO6sX4IHBOGNXZfQaAWKzTIusEtjNITwUW2US6rEmk04p+aSu066rG/H7Ke57zl8MAfrygxfP6WChuHW8DMFSQ2wnoYhgy4A56F+dygwIJAwJgjxIa+ev/WWEx8tgq/KPGoGy2W82eSyfGTAVfBseHd5Mkqjqk+eZ7UxngOYXG3MpnyBBQQKCz7/0jEev8ZCGkLpPVnvV8XdnReRPPHAqBORMRWmEzFNyzzdP1G4RiBKgQIvPRg+niHtV1SEr6EC2a+ollJSNnTGonAvrbYy6ihALynOyV4Ghcc4jIJf+4t7M4Wlzg6Vyc3k+yrP+QafIN3995uKqrhvc2+PqEoO3h8LM5HZdZMxzHSslWPd5FbvznAa/SoTSTNLsRaCLQkrkQKxdMm7cKHthXbl4HVYhli/9OLYoFLtsdvGt3iRkNsAj/KZBQkLdKMFIVx7tTyKvtBUdDlC+L5NZnDdJAEYiiTHWKK+KOtaHrqsN9/cPBHn7qsS7mUQUWAS3XoqUBYanH4NQhRSiWGyQIpgPDZZCeaQTAIv71uX5V5OkeTJmCAWSvOcaB9m5f45X+qnN/3lJw5xSznkBi4Okuc9GhRjOGqTNhZ5dEKk9IWnf/2JTs0xOUX1EFKL5SGcp7wOahR1uxbEFs4GaPKC8m4aOr0N+AJptabMZWYpI3tkJel0SF1cbcQJ/3BKBuQ3tItARdu6QQW7G/fBokpiCvVPYFqVNteYJGtm+zq0McRqff"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18038","langCode":"en","question":"Zh25uzyg9hrP74YtkoJYM/8iMR8maA9qi/VO+Yqlzd21YeIfzRAUsGcSdmWLjBb7","answers":["whose","whom","when","which"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xHeVrZK7KMY2f0hVhY3iQ5Pk9RNfGpxcc2vqmBq8xyZARPiZDPt1bGzARLmW/MJ6fGUGAhSISn9NhApmc0qt0UEkXFOUmtMWmA59PZ//clutehLpW++vG/JCZVkPN3AF8Dol9rooKl1JMW2k2yQ2DTO/Sj3hUX3SqyuCbTr8ZqANOT5H6eFnCgoGj+4VGfuKQ0Ko+n63oB4CYfXmc9alZ9tiVniQL2+5xZE9SSUOKFFHCmVbpzRRTa1+0bAHPmkb6fhBqxv+bcWnHN9kDVn+h/LvZusaMM4G1Da4V2077vhThGW+qEav3HbnRRQD8ue8Hbrl9K9hQWCzfgs1x1aveKt/+8guOBiEa1A/prMnvmSopwPEy1iyy2NEW+ajA90Giy0CysW2ozgJY2+j+n/QOTnU4PhR29EvGf2BjcCn8x56IiS5AxX6ikP84T1k8vm8aQaG7d7kB4G4XMp9T+znpYV/PfrtDAYZ7aSESskuSTMUd3trS58c/iJhkW69QDrLWf2qh6x4qWlSxq5gTdSuOCwB1yOjV2A83N/ejbW0Zo0SYW4nTPYiUvsI1VJb5ZAkcYMlyd/Q88yEkkAAxq9XabQaD6yP7hbHc9FF27SadePn/VZFFIJBiZf/TWJxOgxWEa5Ogd1nJo+AY00eyddOCLx9GszdhLkcz6b4LlkWPyT/2F7IPltg4tkY13mEWXtG1eeWFbecmBX9VFECkb+zazM5QBCRlB9amuMdNKNGfW5e5uja+qlgRxlKszpHiYOe/zVaDFf2ej54nKllz+3nAAnbQSSWDLIQ35zNjHH7DdQboblvuyIWHFMgUtDXek7/urFLplqSEwUM2yblcboqsSeGk1K0rw8TAnlM+Pc7Hggo0w3wIPC1JB9JivuA6xLik1zth1/1dA0oy7ahTPxZAZO6wwIVZ8//or2IJMAvla6L8F69t3t0wG1Iz8NxOLgNg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18039","langCode":"en","question":"bdqjG0NSi1QQpbPIvxh+daw7PU4hby2fZLeUCpRktI452HHBOyvFnov9uxfS2Z/njwJFbtc9bB34pg9U1iQmkQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["whose","where","whom","when"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xHeVrZK7KMY2f0hVhY3iQ5Pk9RNfGpxcc2vqmBq8xyZKrCqp5Bl/Yup6zgI3wRhvtEURk5ugzVjunDUzP0kScsdDje38QiZyzRgIGDh3TJvnrOYLiL8JSpiZlU7TBZvE+ahR1uxbEFs4GaPKC8m4aNtbFiLs6n04LQXpQtxreHaLorPujDIatMw+dGFGUiLT8nT1ewuaWiviQr+DVP5xpYhtPgp4DNSSVywCvYwMc6pVXjmIqFB+s2w6UVUgPP4GQhn110km8GT3SiKePm8LOdpvhYpjvm6ebN+/dtmr3npxukpInwlaLmR8MH92mfxQXC0+Bv9RhZIEaBtJbLMnDNJFIqtW8swdDPLRB1rEtQIkSFRUnPid+qXQNFj96aqdMKp1RMLoVpbLi+U3wVhkqzFa9yTVqn8/CAFCrQVX4OxEv/EK7gI17Tnr+ZDVk5eUTOxdJ4L0tom7eG38fsLWHFQxEialy06fJ0LFP5eEvHu+PRLWp97fdi/JmPFekSzh9VSIOnzhfLORLoMO8gcdQszdvvmTM2qeecxKD2M0ufINHVfZLhPRguzcRyhzsDfOnS766zULs+rD4th8qb4pZ7xlBgIUiEp/TYQKZnNKrdFZGVvvt1wQci0X9gPIj2Hcs4rWULW9W5GwjnynPLd/4x66lk1LkrXuIBiTvkmMkhyqWg1/k74tpdVDa0qWMRvZUeS/BTEBBlqgsEgPJDHy/xsxYfy8QrbO6yP/PkcaZh6KBC6NtpXhU5a14t8qw3yUZ3Q13OxzIjqWU6yIdb2d/VkZW++3XBByLRf2A8iPYdyQPBppkkKFxnzhopjBghknMDol9rooKl1JMW2k2yQ2DSlmuVMMmZH3o2iJ6hbz9yOOTK2Wxtb56RmmpxzRhh6yw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18040","langCode":"en","question":"e/594xpmeUzSqUiFDgYmN/0eU/Ho+H2eSNsXZgtcJwZusAO+ecAnOI1UX8izkTNLODS1aWWHYOZG1wJOz1XNeYcpMIJSsJya0dGjwr9bFcg\u003d","answers":["who","which","whose","when"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xHeVrZK7KMY2f0hVhY3iQ5Pk9RNfGpxcc2vqmBq8xyZlPVPjLrj9Ark2eiUhQXymnI7iv+MuAeBhjYSrpGP29z0No+EEMVHPwDqqIBMOEV3n0rsKekMePe6xbADVvkjlsKSu/5NwhMJFHPAOVu7JGcv0UCQjeO9uo6qb8wK7ez4zlXqfESeEDFJULqOMcHvvflYwEGKZj2DEz4fW/5XPvYOrlDnh78uQIgji+DH9yUBjbfFNsUS5e8shfhcnZKMwDZnipIBwOAOC9dqqPAfz9lrqDlXUQCrfmIXf1LN2staidQglVRoLuJoDAquFJ8qbexaosVi7KMt2ijo/znY/YExnpn+uqDMAQRKVUCS3UJkSYa2aZfYEVSYbHEVNkpSZT4QM1Sz6E8sTOau4m9SbGGnCdF61iyVqvMk5kO2cq/CgzMv9McRkDcczNqkQBoRCOF49x/jucNSeK5wtcLxAaI4LX/bsW0bEIDDWZB8gu3o242p25yYIHlNBPB3KB6CwQulbQril3fXbr+zUeInzqLVjhCw3zcvrnhvH5onqeXJZzbm6/ImMZ8gt08pAeDJwcVl/O7wfv4p67g+CpNPiCQ1pDoKH5j/qFZFDHYIcGr/Q6PGJ9VeaIKPgiO6+TRHK0GO2NBk7FxFu17Rd/eDkJZzdpql5EvZpVIaSa4NEq4ckVPci6XS7DpT1YnZeHKHz9ijBfIOQKUeuFcZ1+2gt6eiLPY8ao1Kte5iMWlW4PSKjEChHAmqnwuxKPNhapPLnIOqjNNDHg7JnnXCJKW1xouidhgUSAG0UKbIvO+e6ndSo5nWyGZN0IJo6JJmPPdPw7up0YrhAnKgt68MzycpnJZHKBNpgpd+MEtFJNvqLMnJIDYu0w6A6Pqa0hjpRHwWej0QuGmIrscxhYqdr5qNMGNXpR2k5C5WlZ9Yi7h0Ih/5a9Gzw+j164nUu8mvtGYB4jtSQizz9tSIN7U18drrKwD9OY2InKUoAkCnSfRADB+jk+4zhFZ44ti+DYzhv7sr8g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18041","langCode":"en","question":"gBXQb5wrTs9xaktaxLx/TnP5f2AEiBuWPxeY24JM16xn/CGepd97KOG8VltiTAmXPYx6Mv9KeUxuGUzJMpCPTA\u003d\u003d","answers":["where","who","whose","when"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xHeVrZK7KMY2f0hVhY3iQ5Pk9RNfGpxcc2vqmBq8xyZUjvIW3GdZc0GRisCLa5SvS7yPZffhjj9VyS7MzQCUfSS1R2U0I+DvgKQ6cWb1BsKpU9Vscfvwk+UXRRDLBxhxxLtQf68h9KfrOOVBEOwySHK4VTFHM5Gnz1wQtn/ayKHtHBJD7wAXGA865iZhncXcSGwFKUVDjFgvBv85cKBg5saoRp3InXt7DWyF2KFoh6V2McLe4PyVItA+EDfJHeTjQS8hTJF0aXpGIuNPZndZi360SSXBCRGQX7ik+orYjXaxwG2lQ7/DCCOA+FriPWggsZ/xsEYbza3yQi0IUIJ/uk5WthOFJSnJluXsvjR0w/L94mGzudt1+YZsnTlR0FxgV8gUH2zIDT/JM6aLy33O9mX4dQ1L57Ph5cekwwX3SIGuNYBwaBSF0DOzLNS8SUXdOQrjqgYMHyOpWtT/HJqX88S+wqeG2ZJcpmH72/Ik303flLuzgJo8GpCQ91uweiNQwowUl3HAoon+if5ODrj73zeyVVJwwDkWGqXsrvDeKL3fWvZbARRvohv4fwTInrMRot8X++i6P2+JeGTopK7C67v01G51QQcDI/Il4MHmu9x/9GiAGoJEeIwTT9iYiroYxi66Sq07+a/R5EKFyhqzzuQ+Jtcre2It1+Ur/gPQFkjf/M3CgYERyAW+RHv1lYQaEqwWkCv+pGIYZKhYAFPS86e7zA1Z0z/gGxxviZ+9r6zXDFJPfJxT5pEjywVRx6TiHI7iv+MuAeBhjYSrpGP29ymUCu9kkJOsQGruK8GQ9BOtK86kCqk84lV1Moc56crRMDol9rooKl1JMW2k2yQ2DT/Xco6tsNh1zMGbKhHOZ96nCIWYDahtdJpu5Iu4s9iRD3P5TQ2l+7aA+klFvGPHVrIWZok+Xyua+zL7y0q+5SZ"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18042","langCode":"en","question":"SyRFssQppGdtHDd2HPbbQFaLS4tB4CQgRmFDrTbgHFe/hRcEgFXMaO4PJf4ur6UOU0M6NtbbmX5uRGvkg3LTZR+kwd7bfkled/qySxmjNGI\u003d","answers":["who","when","which","where"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xHeVrZK7KMY2f0hVhY3iQ5Pk9RNfGpxcc2vqmBq8xyZipoh0WLoupzCS6abVslGBPGUGAhSISn9NhApmc0qt0UEkXFOUmtMWmA59PZ//clutehLpW++vG/JCZVkPN3AF8Dol9rooKl1JMW2k2yQ2DTO/Sj3hUX3SqyuCbTr8ZqANOT5H6eFnCgoGj+4VGfuKQ0Ko+n63oB4CYfXmc9alZ9tiVniQL2+5xZE9SSUOKFFHCmVbpzRRTa1+0bAHPmkb6fhBqxv+bcWnHN9kDVn+h/LvZusaMM4G1Da4V2077vhThGW+qEav3HbnRRQD8ue8Kyu4/FhTm59dWQ+6Nv0/cTVUiDp84XyzkS6DDvIHHULcAxQA9MXkTSmDnM++7m/HSYG0mA6miz5OmHv+rGy2JR0U8oYrfNTcf4z/QCEHN/np4QYaQm6Cj8nC83AZUnU5IUBn/wrrt2xLRbdg8s0DIFxi8Yul4b+7frvN+o7uxtnPv7Aeeu20QVXo95gpyCd5+ahR1uxbEFs4GaPKC8m4aOqx0X6sUswru6+p4HnPKOFD6z/jY3ZNT5R5O0TVYtTT6uHlzevTINHQ0gPbzvF0869XaZcCJt4aUfDqMyG5Etp+S/jC6Wvpt3qdp78qwQekg4BuaMpdD84hDzCWZHyYUucUmQYQmnvT6b694JH47sS43KSNTcR+KQEVfItPHc+4/zQS4V4SBcoC+LV5PYSZkZmSfBqQ7XPw7m7PU9Fi8dMEVaarYTAIPabdmv7UFkEF0BQHIYuAQl+Bl4I1+fH6Z8\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18043","langCode":"en","question":"gbSCwDZQQhE6QMpeImkyweSOm/Mb36BMH3+vcIy4g/BUNHEl+2ZdHo3GFZu7DxUK9SG+A5QVQmI4gYYx35wjs0IshW3ijVa38TkZ2YiQUlw\u003d","answers":["who","that","whose","which"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x13/30D2TcjT62zFUAuCJ5FyxrqN/+SSCWSEBiRVNrC7n46ZJ90NBtEKRdp0/lda5ccuuSbEz9AY51RAkAkmA9+zK4WEJbIKGKk+S0ra0IZn20uORcrt63A4gMbnmR0jgLzR4JG/2Ajc7ZY7kgFaDw55IyZ+391BFILiQlr0oUy52MiOK1y9TJETWS/3iPFZu9O+6YCYtb+HFAWjfsDejvVs5hcbcymfIEFBAoLPv/SMR6/xkIaQuk9We9Xxd2dF5E88cCoE5ExFaYTMU3LPN0/UbhGIEqBAi89GD6eIe1XVISvoQLZr6iWUlI2dMaicC+ttjLqKEAvKc7JXgaFxziMiOjODXilgWSjiEfbW/WS5P+PYLJXmXxXN1hL3ThE/KgiAsx2qk55RFYiuK8gSV/EaT5QsVfh5tEFSCCKVgIY3F3SBYkgK3AjJjwtMC7SABdCUCd7jKtc0a94UV5Xa+RNIBX6FePfp1REmt6WioZgHy+/nf6qJkJjdySk/rwEckpbFt/Nkejk17/NEH/py2gTur3G4a60DvHZaRHTDvYKRFc3aapeRL2aVSGkmuDRKuHJFT3Iul0uw6U9WJ2Xhyh8/YowXyDkClHrhXGdftoLenoiz2PGqNSrXuYjFpVuD0ioxAoRwJqp8LsSjzYWqTy5yDqozTQx4OyZ51wiSltcaLonYYFEgBtFCmyLzvnup3UqOZ1shmTdCCaOiSZjz3T8O7qdGK4QJyoLevDM8nKZyWRygTaYKXfjBLRSTb6izJySA2LtMOgOj6mtIY6UR8Fno9ELhpiK7HMYWKna+ajTBjV6UdpOQuVpWfWIu4dCIf+WvRs8Po9euJ1LvJr7RmAeI7UkIs8/bUiDe1NfHa6ysA/TmNiJylKAJAp0n0QAwfo6OeRjIuj0ze0D4lZaA+lfs\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18044","langCode":"en","question":"Yp/pPgTgyzSgmeg8U2PuYItPL0yZowHlaVC0RcZfVBWNZ/DA/mNfDCj2CjYkxKrg4FFoqpbAGQiyn/HecOnfrQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["why","Ø","who","whose"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14iuBOmO5fpiJLF1DNWsQEEZzzwxTHe5NZd9xtZke9ObEVrReZ4Z3dhddWrx0vVcP/ZbBIHLyqo7q3hj1RXlxBbhNGAXqUijAU1YRIo/6WXniL16xlzAvZkuVH1XyC00NqKcDxMtYsstjRFvmowPdBqlJAfHu338HzprOG5RpeUP1QGK/3GEI6c5dX6yK3q+YkMaoHkCvSgz+9M7Sa5ra5qVxJYjeMgqSFPJOd0Eugh+TCT+5/iTVSjc+kXa23fQiQTm8nWbcpF9R81S8sgSRkX/QDaviZbG7k8a2l2vvhPWGH/gXPD0SE1ffXZtJlvsbHUyJ62TOYHEd4G5hQqIihSb1u7/1LomAVq+hdy2yGj0qd5kfixC2eEQRKtGcnroQ7OQbVQElRJWn8L4AU/M4n+8G29FzIdd/9/t8Tv3hqsAB1WIZYv/Ti2KBS7bHbxrd4kZDbAI/ymQUJC3SjBSFce7U8ir7QVHQ5Qvi+TWZw3SQBGIokx1iivijrWh66rDff3DwR5+6rEu5lEFFgEt16KlAWGpx+DUIUUolhskCKYDw2WQnmkEwCL+9bl+VeTpHkyZggFkrznGgfZuX+OV/qpzf95ScOcUs55AYuDpLnPRoUYzhqkzYWeXRCpPSFp3/9iU7NMTlF9RBSi+UhnKe8DmoUdbsWxBbOBmjygvJuGjq9DfgCabWmzGVmKSN7ZCXpdEhdXG3ECf9wSgbkN7SLQEXbukEFuxv3waJKYgr1T24C4oI2Ij9dQ9ODE2AQKteKAjNfnsu8hZcYx9lVDbJMvak4rhpRf5tTuRU3YQyUDptaN9tIL6S61ERhBoglBPjAtGuPwzbRA+Hphn66BjZpm8+aFiVCSrBvXtDd6Rgqq0"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18045","langCode":"en","question":"uy8AguMG/0fBi/DeMWQFpYIJZvUk/HvF/5D/RTF3xssZArLPu6yFt7PPJcMjpWFXzNwc6dZFwHu5uWfR1ZOhcQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","where","whose","Ø"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14iuBOmO5fpiJLF1DNWsQEEZzzwxTHe5NZd9xtZke9ObEVrReZ4Z3dhddWrx0vVcP/ZbBIHLyqo7q3hj1RXlxBbhNGAXqUijAU1YRIo/6WXniL16xlzAvZkuVH1XyC00NqKcDxMtYsstjRFvmowPdBrJSz5EeqzbWV0xmqswu/Ab0dbe0+ywx34sSvgd+NJdTvhWb2Cf2um16VB52FvTdEoegrb63KXvyQ3qASH7SHQb7l4CDTsNZPCa6sEVbjvsbvEzscmDVmrY0nK8tBPtQbGII+NC6Ruqj27CYWXryGwXdPVIropwo3Tj+DjkVJD2F3RbRQBGJmYIXv+dQa5Zf5HjL6EiZCRpl064JwIXq2P/6ZnaG91ZEI4gcmOfXKiVsafE7IeSIv0AtVqeZZX8OdFKDzoXfgH4+ysFhezxQ1B83jjOmlFnldweDihmvUTcCG/o1cuLGVXpwBeLcMNAyb46AN0GPQzt5z7rYI6ITYSBRygTaYKXfjBLRSTb6izJyWLck0MJPsJ7My0O62yMOrNhEa23zSFla+SPI6JjDamQa/X6NWP4NaOECs1Rg+AbtetayJWoQ0NUXA2gP/MkirqqyFXZslFowkI24J6Q7s5eGABjKQmGJfwZ5m1hc+gOLX5pGFvZU5crS0UegiJz0GbivTDM++7uqO0YxFwsRX5Tdho0cd6XHajUZ2TnDzr7Xa2MEm/FNWbxQhandXNPl4gbS7HIPAgDh4cQlznm6W7EXDNW4f0zN8v93PycwdLoQsDRrlNmAeE8FF4i3NEnJmBeb5cajbncs1qTfm8t4upPfuqpZzq++sOchRA+/S3mYPoxmVEhZgQwb7nmura9X+YY1Pt+5VQ9SgrOwHzO9A36LEajhx029ckGXmTBhkq8DBk/wDJz0eEZzaovXn0cDv6TmjhvY6nWfLJa/XiCOwKF36sEACDi/QxQgMw0/Gtq8g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18046","langCode":"en","question":"p5mTCSXQe1r+ZUk/KowMABBVmHhyn6m+533w8UpWMxf3rnDBDnlBKIAzYaFrDJwkSnUTKfnE45xcElyEaWGJlA\u003d\u003d","answers":["whose","which","who","that"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x13/30D2TcjT62zFUAuCJ5Fw8uFwvTi8tiM0QuIRAAX5rZyFTtZugqkgo//oJP415wuS+uORU85e2cuUxruVSt4sxcCNQLjZagueGodnCJVWjkRgxckUNTT1dd54GyMI57W2N82p/7LS2S1CLu1/7RgWxsmH4gi48IvSk0dWuddtfmOOZfSBJuVgCdgin91Nq4V8wj/6td26+4gS76f/SJhJbdhFWl8VNX814SIhogW2yUIc6B2SzT2z/POphb9aZZYE89ZCkVq7mcgHWRIaXS5r5rqlqfwO3Xy6J2s9CE+bcYFHaBpJBZFva9LL3k5Sczww5lF1L6W22hakEtDzz4fbqSLZ+IBDgXh8a7ck+5wgdj44S6Vwm393OUAtl8XTuW4vSMgAXWyvZUQbuZKUFGfSEcBdRryePebnbs0nto56KZNK0Jse7KBl2Lh/jZ4WlGR6xsUh8vj/JRmHLyJFPYI2HtrX7KgsIwNp9kTAvWXwQAzEQZmQGvWEs3Z7J5/00EfnkGJ075yBUP6oPMH+5SjPuU+n2CLk6Nj29dXt3pHBU7GQe/3VMefOoCje9MUxFnQgBKQ12TTP4cTDCtAei7w0u/TK2chNu+jxg+fA+Oc9HACQuMFCTUIaHWDqfxalg+XrsPGRymlCyeoqKOense9GyFjjS3FE1RYV+DAWKVjuXcYvGLpeG/u367zfqO7sbZyJCNp3S6XKbo37G/HJs49wmvaJW3yVE4x8xAa5vr9zVmjZiQcgVL0D/xnNYe/A6D/wcPWZGcirfBz18l6hU/Z4TZ4fMlBRx/RsxXgMF0PcV5kbwQPZwiikWIO+U/xCVjg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18047","langCode":"en","question":"OYhLOc0BHe0EtNp13CvaSCqSK+UU7pkgcMRSuDGx8nqu4n1HonqIyQ8rQr4WZdeOXeB+IjoIcvbBZWaAtVeImw\u003d\u003d","answers":["Ø","which","where","whose"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14iuBOmO5fpiJLF1DNWsQEEZzzwxTHe5NZd9xtZke9ObEVrReZ4Z3dhddWrx0vVcP/ZbBIHLyqo7q3hj1RXlxBbhNGAXqUijAU1YRIo/6WXniL16xlzAvZkuVH1XyC00NqKcDxMtYsstjRFvmowPdBrJSz5EeqzbWV0xmqswu/Ab0dbe0+ywx34sSvgd+NJdTvhWb2Cf2um16VB52FvTdEoegrb63KXvyQ3qASH7SHQb7l4CDTsNZPCa6sEVbjvsbvEzscmDVmrY0nK8tBPtQbGII+NC6Ruqj27CYWXryGwXdPVIropwo3Tj+DjkVJD2F3RbRQBGJmYIXv+dQa5Zf5HjL6EiZCRpl064JwIXq2P/6ZnaG91ZEI4gcmOfXKiVsafE7IeSIv0AtVqeZZX8OdFKDzoXfgH4+ysFhezxQ1B83jjOmlFnldweDihmvUTcCG/o1cuLGVXpwBeLcMNAyb46AN0GPQzt5z7rYI6ITYSBRygTaYKXfjBLRSTb6izJyWLck0MJPsJ7My0O62yMOrNhEa23zSFla+SPI6JjDamQa/X6NWP4NaOECs1Rg+AbtetayJWoQ0NUXA2gP/MkirqqyFXZslFowkI24J6Q7s5eGABjKQmGJfwZ5m1hc+gOLX5pGFvZU5crS0UegiJz0GbivTDM++7uqO0YxFwsRX5Tdho0cd6XHajUZ2TnDzr7Xa2MEm/FNWbxQhandXNPl4gbS7HIPAgDh4cQlznm6W7EXDNW4f0zN8v93PycwdLoQsDRrlNmAeE8FF4i3NEnJmBeb5cajbncs1qTfm8t4upPfuqpZzq++sOchRA+/S3mYPoxmVEhZgQwb7nmura9X+YY1Pt+5VQ9SgrOwHzO9A36LEajhx029ckGXmTBhkq8DBk/wDJz0eEZzaovXn0cDv6TmjhvY6nWfLJa/XiCOwKF36sEACDi/QxQgMw0/Gtq8g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18048","langCode":"en","question":"uy8AguMG/0fBi/DeMWQFpdnQgvqLARvCxaFQ0kky19CsWpH0fJVY4U8dtoUIhXv2+YJLH2Z0rtMBKkWxU7jSxw\u003d\u003d","answers":["why","whose","Ø","which"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14iuBOmO5fpiJLF1DNWsQEEZzzwxTHe5NZd9xtZke9ObEVrReZ4Z3dhddWrx0vVcP/ZbBIHLyqo7q3hj1RXlxBbhNGAXqUijAU1YRIo/6WXniL16xlzAvZkuVH1XyC00NqKcDxMtYsstjRFvmowPdBqlJAfHu338HzprOG5RpeUP1QGK/3GEI6c5dX6yK3q+YkMaoHkCvSgz+9M7Sa5ra5qVxJYjeMgqSFPJOd0Eugh+TCT+5/iTVSjc+kXa23fQiQTm8nWbcpF9R81S8sgSRkWyqq6fZWzcitAwr7V2qyct+PYLJXmXxXN1hL3ThE/KgiAsx2qk55RFYiuK8gSV/EaT5QsVfh5tEFSCCKVgIY3F3SBYkgK3AjJjwtMC7SABdCUCd7jKtc0a94UV5Xa+RNIBX6FePfp1REmt6WioZgHy+/nf6qJkJjdySk/rwEckpbFt/Nkejk17/NEH/py2gTur3G4a60DvHZaRHTDvYKRFc3aapeRL2aVSGkmuDRKuHJFT3Iul0uw6U9WJ2Xhyh8/YowXyDkClHrhXGdftoLenoiz2PGqNSrXuYjFpVuD0ioxAoRwJqp8LsSjzYWqTy5yDqozTQx4OyZ51wiSltcaLonYYFEgBtFCmyLzvnup3UqOZ1shmTdCCaOiSZjz3T8O7qdGK4QJyoLevDM8nKZyWRygTaYKXfjBLRSTb6izJySA2LtMOgOj6mtIY6UR8Fno9ELhpiK7HMYWKna+ajTBjV6UdpOQuVpWfWIu4dCIf+WvRs8Po9euJ1LvJr7RmAeI7UkIs8/bUiDe1NfHa6ysA/TmNiJylKAJAp0n0QAwfo6ezk4NNf8BpShJl/M8vTuu27yQeivP1+12cLIrrjD+wBoJBiisVVAe9xQElb1ytAniR3reDp+eQAdReL9bOjsYaif4CyS3ZULb6352ULCC+"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18049","langCode":"en","question":"ePqI6yKVuWIeurvwtMrQxL4WhPzYpC6w8UHd4uPxzaLbc7ppp2twjl6HrUmpdU0x","answers":["why","whose","who","Ø"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14iuBOmO5fpiJLF1DNWsQEEZzzwxTHe5NZd9xtZke9ObEVrReZ4Z3dhddWrx0vVcP/ZbBIHLyqo7q3hj1RXlxBYEXw4v41b7UBp+zPkL1e/pwA3B2mlVKstIS+4KJC3UnJfSQLKTncwwK7Pcn0ShPNbTrPBd1fYDc8nzOh0FjRiTk/w7UI5SeUX8dV36dZjS5sxJUMe/vpNytPJ4BD4QfganLLxg5RXu2atFOO397wEstKjCSTsq5mb5C4pkrnNpqwnodSC9wRbSzM/Tj1YIhv4ohxa5rE9Q/FwEHUI2b+TUpwnRetYslarzJOZDtnKvwoMzL/THEZA3HMzapEAaEQhD6vIJKl8ziyC6NWm6uxtIz+SkI826jDJjO1g2OCEtFOK0D6y0G7YDXW2gFw9qB+Hstc343gCebLEr2mGyrubljLDjfOiw3RCOdTyww5Tuc/ZbBIHLyqo7q3hj1RXlxBY6zXI6sBSHroYU99lHQaNT1Q4JFJfy4pVZxLSTXUTKO+FPBZ/PL5gHkmAKfRZFj9GribUavvHC9JrxgbTpU0O+FKSiIRJDljgnjnC8yASotZGarkrj8/t5gqpzBurbcdgKMFJdxwKKJ/on+Tg64+98utYiOzcV3k6Tr/mzkOc2opDySobKnZsw3NAWqgmsSLGIyWPJBJAzFO5agOrmSGF3IaOW2X8vSrt8DfAW7EXu7+VIx1kF1bFX2isoCexSOyZoRGeLWZ9MyLKMyQ2w3goGUCPRgGa7FOPl52TJSX83GgvaxjyOfQ6xCJicaVWEUu0sC/pWQtzmrpiDjqWKc5ax"},{"topicId":"18","id":"18050","langCode":"en","question":"AWwLiIf9OQkJuvL7dgaDZ+5H3lRn1yIaFX6rVjBVibuxZ+vVFeV1S+i8/G4ObVFF","answers":["leaves","left","to leave","leave"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x11qoOBH5s9rSnnEk0w6cG2Ml9/BruwDivp/XXv5UwnBa9lsEgcvKqjureGPVFeXEFkmysdQ7SeRGW31mAOqa53kkaYQq4WI6UC9pl5Sh0b+twaI5ClyQ9NGjyye5/Vm4yCca/kpS8Hsw5h3ir3//j8/dgf931HBiLHJtEVtGu6Ya"}]